OK.
好的。
Hi, guys. Good morning.
嗨，大家好。 早上好。
Good evening, everybody.
晚上好大家。
How's it going?
怎么样了？
What's up? What's up?
怎么了？ 怎么了？
Y'all doing good?
你们都好吗？
Everyone. Everyone. Chilling.
每个人。 每个人。 不寒而栗。
Everyone
每个人
have dinner.
吃晚饭。
You better have had dinner.
你最好吃过晚饭。
I saw so many people last night. They're complaining about they.
昨晚见了这么多人。 他们在抱怨他们。
Didn't have dinner, so.
没吃晚饭，所以。
I feel, like, inclined to ask and make sure, like, y'all eat before you stream.
我觉得，就像，倾向于询问并确保，就像，你们都在流式传输之前吃完。
I know.
我知道。
I did.
我做到了。
OK, so that's another thing.
好的，那是另一回事。
Like, I've been in such a good habit lately of making sure
就像，我最近一直有一个很好的习惯来确保
I have a meal before any of my streams and.
我在我的任何溪流之前吃饭。
I don't know.
我不知道。
It seems like something small, but I'm really proud of myself
这似乎是一件小事，但我真的为自己感到骄傲
because I don't really usually, I don't know, have good habits I guess.
因为我真的不平时，我不知道，我猜有好习惯。
So it makes me happy that I'm able to, like, keep up that routine.
所以我很高兴我能够保持这种习惯。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
So I wanted to talk about something real quick, but hold on
所以我想快速谈谈一些真正的事情，但请稍等
Oh, yeah.
有一些，我猜。 猜鸡块。
Thank you for the 521.
谢谢你的521。
And and I thinking of the 5000 and midnight.
我想到了 5000 和午夜。
Thank you for the sincere ones.
谢谢那些真诚的人。
Good morning, guys.
早上好家伙。
Hope you are having a great day.
希望你有一个美好的一天。
Lately, I've been in, like,
最近，我一直在玩神奇宝贝的这种奇怪的心情，我不知道为什么。
Like, there's just something in my head that's, like, telling me,
就像，我脑子里有一些东西，就像，告诉我，
oh, you should do a nose lock again. Shuffle.
哦，你应该再做一个鼻子锁。 随机播放。
And, like, I don't even know, like, what game I would nose lock in.
而且，就像，我什至不知道，我会锁定什么游戏。
Like, I don't know.
像，我不知道。
Maybe something about pokemon pokemon heart, golden souls, or like,
也许是关于 pokemon pokemon heart、golden
pokemon emeralds, or maybe even
souls 之类的 pokemon 翡翠，或者甚至
Pokemon Platinum, but I'm not sure.
口袋妖怪白金，但我不确定。
I don't know. It's.
我不知道。 它的。
It's like nothing. I don't think I would stream.
它就像什么都没有。 我不认为我会流。
It's more like something I would do on my own time just to chill and relax.
这更像是我会在自己的时间做的事情，只是为了放松和放松。
But yeah, I haven't played a good.
但是，是的，我没有打好。
Pokemon game in a while, and I don't know, I haven't finished Legends of Arceus
口袋妖怪游戏有一段时间了，我不知道，我还没有完成阿尔宙斯的传说
as just like I barely had the time to like or like my vision, so I want to hop on.
就像我几乎没有时间喜欢或喜欢我的愿景一样，所以我想继续前进。
That. Oh, yeah.
那。 哦耶。
So I wanted to talk about this really quickly
所以我想很快地谈论这个
while, you know, people are coming in.
同时，你知道，人们正在进来。
But I realised.
但我意识到了。
That I don't know, like after what, a year plus a shooting,
那我不知道，就像在什么之后，一年加上一次拍摄，所花的一切就像某人
to email to let me know like, hey,
发电子邮件让我知道，嘿，
so people can't donate because some people don't have people, right?
所以人们可以捐款，因为有些人没有人，对吧？
And that makes sense.
这是有道理的。
So what I ended up doing was checking.
所以我最终做的是检查。
I was like, Oh wait.
我当时想，哦等等。
I can set up my accounts to take like donations from like cards and stuff.
我可以设置我的帐户以从类似的卡片和其他东西中获取类似的捐款。
And I never knew that.
我从来不知道。
So on Twitter, Tilda.
所以在推特上，蒂尔达。
Oh, thank you so much, dude.
哦，太谢谢你了，伙计。
Yeah, we have friends again.
是的，我们又有朋友了。
Sort of like, was it a few days ago?
有点像，是几天前吗？
So it makes me really happy. And we're getting.
所以这让我真的很开心。 我们得到了。
Close to half a million, too. Oh, my gosh. I don't even know.
也接近一百万。 天啊。 我根本不知道。
I would do a half a million.
我会做一百万。
I know that for YouTube.
对于 YouTube，我知道这一点。
I said that on YouTube, if we have 400, then I'll do a getting over extreme.
我在 YouTube 上说过，如果我们有 400 个，那么我会做一个越过极限的。
But ah, I don't know.
但是啊，我不知道。
It doesn't seem as painful
它似乎不像 Jump King 或其他人那样痛苦，但他们知道
like a lot of people struggle with getting over it.
就像很多人都在努力克服它。
But I don't know.
但是我不知道。
I have a.
我有一个。
Feeling that after watching so many streams of getting over it,
感觉看了这么多的流过之后，
I'll be able to like take those techniques that people learnt
我将能够喜欢人们学到的那些技术
and just like use on my own to try and, you know,
就像我自己尝试使用一样，你知道，
make it to the top because you know, that game is hard.
登上顶峰，因为你知道，那场比赛很难。
It's pretty damn hard for people that you know,
你认识的人真的太难了
just starting off.
刚刚开始。
It's like a whole trial and error process, so.
这就像一个完整的试错过程，所以。
But right back.
但是马上回来。
That's what I was talking about.
这就是我所说的。
So I realised like it was really hard for people to like,
所以我意识到人们真的很难喜欢，你知道，如果他们愿意，直接支持流
through the channels and stuff like that.
通过渠道和类似的东西。
So what I ended up doing was that if you do want to donate,
所以我最终做的是，如果你真的想捐款，你现在可以通过一张通行卡来做
instead of like doing it to through PayPal.
而不是喜欢通过 PayPal 来做。
So you have like two options through PayPal or through
因此，您有两种选择，通过 PayPal 或通过
your own card.
你自己的卡。
So it's just I was.
所以这只是我。
I was dumb, I was stupid.
我很笨，我很笨。
I didn't realise like that was an option this entire time.
我一直没有意识到这是一个选择。
So it's there now, it's because it's also less inconvenient for other people.
所以它现在就在那里，这是因为它对其他人来说也不那么不方便。
So I'm so sorry about that.
所以我对此感到非常抱歉。
I didn't know like I could set that up this entire time and, and here like.
我不知道我是否可以一直设置它，并且在这里。
You know, some people.
你知道，有些人。
Don't use PayPal, so that's another thing.
不要使用贝宝，这是另一回事。
But yeah, this. Is an option now.
但是，是的，这个。 现在是一种选择。
And if you want so like not lose money to, to watch and all that stuff.
如果你想不赔钱，观看和所有这些东西。
But yeah, my apologies.
但是，是的，我很抱歉。
I don't know. I'm a dumb boy. I'm one big dumb boy.
我不知道。 我是个傻孩子。 我是一个大笨男孩。
I didn't, I didn't realise like I could have that as a donation option.
我没有，我没有意识到我可以将其作为捐赠选择。
So yeah, it's there now.
所以，是的，它现在就在那里。
So I hope it works and I hope it's OK.
所以我希望它有效，我希望它没问题。
I don't know if there's any issues I don't think there's going to be any issue.
我不知道是否有任何问题我认为不会有任何问题。
So it should be able to work.
所以它应该能够工作。
And if it doesn't, then let me know. OK?
如果没有，请告诉我。 好的？
Sorry. Zoe.
对不起。 佐伊。
Yeah, because
是的，因为
it was really.
这是真的。
Like I said before, it was really inconvenient for some people.
就像我之前说的，这对某些人来说真的很不方便。
So, you know, wants to help and support their dreams and whatever.
所以，你知道，想要帮助和支持他们的梦想等等。
So yeah, it's, it's there now, so it should be a lot easier to do so
所以，是的，它现在就在那里，所以这样做应该容易得多
for everybody.
为所有人。
That's you know,
那就是你知道，
that doesn't have people and like, you know, doesn't use people.
没有人和喜欢，你知道，不使用人。
So those are set up.
所以这些都设置好了。
But I'm some like I'm stupid, so.
但是我有点像我很愚蠢，所以。
Yeah.
是的。
OK, but
好的，但是啊，今天我们将永远玩一些。
I've never touch this website or game before.
我以前从未接触过这个网站或游戏。
It has been like, I've seen it
就像，我在 switch 和
the my recommended.
我推荐的。
Because people.
因为人。
Do like, I think this
喜欢，我觉得这个
I tried it and look I've tried it and like of other few like big streamers,
我试过了，看起来我已经试过了，就像其他几个像大飘带一样，
it's like a crane game stuff, right?
就像起重机游戏一样，对吧？
It'll satisfy my needs to do crane games without actually
它可以满足我做起重机游戏的需要，而不必去街机玩。
So like if,
所以，如果我想去喜欢第一轮或其他街机游戏，那就是韩国游戏。
I don't need to do that. I could just do it at home.
我不需要这样做。 我只能在家里做。
But I heard that it's hard.
但是听说很难。
It's like really hard to get a good price.
很难买到好价钱。
But you. Know what? That's why.
但是你。 知道什么？ 因此。
That's why we have, we have the power of of money.
这就是为什么我们拥有，我们拥有金钱的力量。
Question mark, I think.
问号，我想。
And I don't know.
我不知道。
Maybe I've seen videos of it, but.
也许我看过它的视频，但是。
There's like a people that work there, I can help you out, too.
那里有人工作，我也可以帮你。
I think that's pretty cool.
我认为这很酷。
Like, you know, if they see you struggling, they'll be like, hey,
就像，你知道的，如果他们看到你在挣扎，他们会说，嘿，
you need some help here.
你需要一些帮助。
And they just, like, grab it and like loosen it up for you.
他们只是，喜欢，抓住它，喜欢为你松开它。
I think that's really sweet, but I don't know if I'll get that lucky.
我觉得这真的很甜蜜，但我不知道我是否会得到那种幸运。
Okay, we're going to try and try and we'll see what happens.
好的，我们将尝试并尝试，我们会看到会发生什么。
Oh, it's it's really it's.
哦，原来如此。
Really cool.
真的很酷。
Like, I've never tried this before, but I've always wanted to get, like,
就像，我以前从未尝试过，但我一直想从其中一个我不知道的东西中得到一些东西
if I want to do a figurine or a plushy or, like, there's, like, other stuff, too.
如果我想做一个小雕像或毛绒玩具，或者像，还有其他东西。
There's a heater here. What's.
这里有暖气。 什么是。
I see a.
我看到一个。
Lot of cushions and pillows and toys.
很多靠垫和枕头和玩具。
But I don't know, there's even all this.
但我不知道，甚至还有这一切。
This is a Siberian husky.
这是一只西伯利亚雪橇犬。
Big, plush, and super adorable, and I think I should switch
大，毛绒，超级可爱，我想我应该切换到游戏或网站。
And then you guys can see.
然后你们就可以看到了。
On this great beat you.
在这个伟大的击败你。
Congrats on 400. Okay. Less than three.
恭喜400。好的。 不到三个。
Credit card is great.
信用卡很棒。
Oh, wait.
等一下。
Yeah, I said that you are okay.
是的，我说你没事。
It works, Pug.
它有效，帕格。
All right. Awesome. Thank you so much, dude.
好的。 惊人的。 非常感谢你，伙计。
Yeah,
是的，
I appreciate the I appreciate the demo, and thank you for the congratulations.
我很欣赏我欣赏演示，并感谢您的祝贺。
It means a lot
那意义重大
hitting a lot of milestones recently.
最近达到了很多里程碑。
This is spooky, but I really hope that, you know, it's.
这很吓人，但我真的希望，你知道，它是。
Ah, it'll be.
啊，会的。
Oh, I don't know.
哦我不知道。
There's a lot of.
有很多。
Them, so I want to see, like, big celebrations for, um, for a few.
他们，所以我想看到，比如，为少数人举办的大型庆祝活动。
Oh, so hold on.
哦，那就等着吧。
Give me a second.
你稍等一会儿。
Let me turn on some
让我打开一些
and turn some music
并打开一些音乐，这样我们就可以冷静下来
something. Uh,
某物。 呃，
when we get over to the game.
当我们开始比赛时。
What is this.
这是什么。
Yeah, I'm at a party.
是的，我正在参加一个聚会。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
I don't listen to that.
我不听那个。
OK. OK, sure.
好的。 好的。
I'll put this on. It sounds. Sounds chill.
我会穿上这个的。 听起来。 听起来很冷。
I was like, what the.
我当时想，什么。
All right, hold on.
好吧，等一下。
Give me a second.
你稍等一会儿。
I'm going to switch over to crane game screen.
我要切换到起重机游戏画面。
So give me give me a little bit.
所以给我一点点。
Also, I hope everyone's been having a great. Week, so far.
另外，我希望每个人都过得很好。 一周，到此为止。
It's already Thursday.
已经是星期四了。
Tomorrow is our karaoke stream, too, so it's going to be really,
明天也是我们的卡拉OK直播，所以真的，
really exciting to get to draw some new songs of you guys.
能画出你们的新歌真的很令人兴奋。
I have like.
我有喜欢。
I like 20 something songs I think prepared.
我喜欢我认为准备好的 20 首歌曲。
It's a try live on stream tomorrow, so you better be there.
明天将在现场直播，所以你最好到场。
It's going to be a big celebration.
这将是一个盛大的庆祝活动。
I think I might get some some soju.
我想我可能会得到一些烧酒。
So like, you know, it's like drink during the karaoke and probably order some
所以就像，你知道的，这就像在卡拉 OK 的时候喝酒，可能会点一些
some good food like, like wings or whatever.
一些好吃的食物，比如翅膀之类的。
That sounds nice.
听起来不错。
All right.
好的。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
Let me see.
让我看看。
Where is forever?
永远在哪里？
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Hold on. Don't look at me for a second, OK? I guess. Yeah.
坚持，稍等。 不要看我一秒钟，好吗？ 我猜。 是的。
You know, perceive on
你知道，感知
I just have to make myself look.
我只需要让自己看起来。
Like every time.
就像每次一样。
Every single time.
每一次。
You guys think you're so funny.
你们觉得自己很有趣。
You guys think you're.
你们以为是。
So fucking funny. Ha,
真他妈好笑。 哈，
you clowns.
你们这些小丑。
All your clowns.
你所有的小丑。
Come on, man. What
来吧，伙计。 什么
Oh, hold on.
哦，等一下。
OK. OK, I'm going to come.
好的。 好的，我去。
All right?
好的？
You control.
你控制。
Control yourself there, buddy.
在那里控制自己，伙计。
Buddy,
伙伴，
all right.
好的。
Can you see this?
你能看到这个吗？
You guys see it on my screen? Hello.
你们在我的屏幕上看到了吗？ 你好。
I might as well go.
我还不如去。
All of you wrote it down, uncle, since we don't need that anymore for today,
你们都把它写下来了，叔叔，因为今天我们不再需要它了，
everything looks good.
一切看起来都很好。
Nice. You can see this, right?
好的。 你可以看到这个，对吧？
OK. Ah, hold on.
好的。 啊，等一下。
Let me also let me check on a couple more things just to make sure
让我也让我再检查几件事，以确保
we are chillin.
我们很冷。
Yeah, we're fine right now.
是的，我们现在很好。
Oh, I think it's ok.
哦，我觉得还可以。
Maybe bigger deal, maybe bigger pop.
也许更大的交易，也许更大的流行。
A sound so bad our contacts.
声音太糟糕了我们的联系方式。
You want me to get bigger for you, babe?
你想让我为你变大吗，宝贝？
Like, no.
就像，没有。
All right.
好的。
I think this is good enough.
我认为这已经足够好了。
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah, it feels good enough.
是的，感觉还不错。
All right.
好的。
So I. I don't. Know.
所以我。我没有。 知道。
It's this spring seal right here.
就是这个弹簧密封件就在这里。
Collection card
收藏卡
ah. 10,000 tape.
啊。  10,000 个磁带。
What is this one?
这是什么？
No prises will be delivered.
不会提供任何奖品。
What's was that mean?
那是什么意思？
I don't.
我不。
I don't understand what this is.
我不明白这是什么。
Is this, like, supposed.
这是，像，应该的。
To be free, huh?
要自由，嗯？
I'm not sure.
我不确定。
Earned CP yeah, I guess.
赢了CP是的，我猜。
Because, like, zip is the the currency that, uh,
因为，就像，zip 是一种货币，呃，
you know, people will use or like, they use for the young for the game.
要知道，人们会使用或喜欢，他们为年轻人使用的游戏。
We go back to the page.
我们回到页面。
All they have are.
他们所有的都是。
Was it was she sure your idea is how she sure as a figurine.
是她确定你的想法是她如何确定作为一个小雕像。
As I'll hold up.
因为我会坚持。
What is this, a cute. Little otter.
这是什么东西，可爱。 小水獭。
You don't cushion cushion cushion
你不坐垫坐垫
as southern goal as a big arse elephant.
像一头大驴一样的南方目标。
And there's also a REM hold up.
还有一个 REM 暂停。
Wait, they have ram.
等等，他们有公羊。
What else do I got? Oh,
我还有什么？ 哦，
yeah. There's also, like, a dog.
是的。 还有，比如，一只狗。
I want this one.
我要这个。
I want this one so bad. OK, ok.
我太想要这个了。 好的好的。
We're going for the dog. I want the dog. We're going for the dog.
我们去找狗。 我要那条狗。 我们去找狗。
Hello?
你好？
I want the fucking dog.
我要那条该死的狗。
Look at him. He's so big. 75 centimetres.
看着他。 他那么大。  75 厘米。
How big is 75 centimetres.
75厘米有多大。
I I think that's pretty big, right.
我认为这很大，对吧。
That's a big dog toy or dog plush, whatever it is.
那是一个大狗玩具或狗毛绒，不管它是什么。
It's huge.
这是巨大的。
Yeah. He's, he's pretty huge.
是的。 他，他的体型很大。
Oh what is this.
哦，这是什么。
Oh yeah. Right. The background music.
哦耶。 对。 背景音乐。
I know it's loud.
我知道声音很大。
I didn't know how long it was going to be so I put it down a bit.
我不知道它会持续多久，所以我把它放下了一点。
Let's look at him.
让我们看看他。
Let's look at the boy.
让我们看看男孩。
He's so big oh, my God, bro.
他好大哦，天哪，兄弟。
Roar.
怒吼。
I want it, I want it.
我想要它，我想要它。
I want him. Can I get him?
我要他。 我能得到他吗？
Is it possible, d is this possible to get somebody I don't know.
有没有可能，d 这有可能得到一个我不认识的人。
Who's the expert on this game, do you think? Is this.
谁是这个游戏的专家，你觉得呢？ 这是。
Is this. Ah, can I do it?
这是。 啊，我可以吗？
Yes, I can.
我可以。
It's it's possible. It's possible.
这是可能的。 有可能的。
OK, ok. OK, let's try.
好的好的。 好的，我们试试。
Let's try.
咱们试试吧。
I'll know I'll know.
我会知道我会知道的。
Bro's
兄弟的
all right.
好的。
I've played tickets, right?
我打过票对吧？
I guess
我猜
I ah. I
我啊。 一世
I hope this music.
我希望这个音乐。
Isn't DMCA, is it?
不是 DMCA，是吗？
It seems fine.
看起来不错。
OK. Oh, I'm timed.
好的。 哦，我是定时的。
Wait, there's a timer.
等等，有一个计时器。
Why do I have a timer for ah.
为什么我有一个定时器啊。
OK, so I have a points.
好的，所以我有一点。
I guess I charges. He's the points, I guess. Sure.
我想我收费。 我猜他是积分。 当然。
I'll use the ticket.
我会用票。
Oh, he can go see my mouse.
哦，他可以去看我的鼠标。
Give me a ticket.
给我一张票。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Oh, there it is. OK,
哦，是的。 好的，给你。
I think you should be able to see it now.
我想你现在应该可以看到了。
Yeah, there it is. Powers.
是的，就是这样。 权力。
OK, wait.
好，等一下。
I don't have time
我没时间
what is that?
那是什么？
Hold,
抓住，
dude. Hold on, hold on.
老兄。 等一下，等一下。
What is. That? What is that?
什么是。 那？ 那是什么？
It didn't even move at all.
它甚至根本不动。
Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。
Oh, no. OK, ok,
不好了。 好的好的，
ok. Ah. Ah.
行。 啊。 啊。
If someone give me advice, should I push it forward?
如果有人给我建议，我应该推动它吗？
Maybe I should push it.
也许我应该推动它。
With the claw
用爪子
it's a scam.
这是一个骗局。
I share the scam.
我分享这个骗局。
I can move it to the left or to the right.
我可以将它向左或向右移动。
Oh, I think I know why I got you. I got to like.
哦，我想我知道我为什么得到你了。 我不得不喜欢。
I got to like shimmied my way over to the hole, right?
我得喜欢晃晃晃晃地走到洞口，对吧？
So then it can get inside my hole on or the whole the whole, not my whole.
所以它可以进入我的洞里或整个整体，而不是我的整体。
What's emotion no damage.
什么是情感没有伤害。
OK, cool.
嗯不错。
Like that.
像那样。
And then.
进而。
I know yeah, yeah. Push.
我知道是的，是的。 推。
Push it, push it. No.
推，推。 不。
What am I.
我是什么。
That's so hard.
那太难了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I don't know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办。
The bite.
咬。
Oh, yeah. I should go for the the. Buy it.
哦耶。 我应该去的。 买它。
Push the head.
推头。
I can't push the head. Like it doesn't want me.
我推不了头。 就像它不要我一样。
It doesn't let me go further like it won't let me.
它不会让我走得更远，就像它不会让我一样。
I'm trying.
我在尝试。
So, like, I thought I could, like, pick it up in the middle, but it the.
所以，就像，我想我可以，喜欢，在中间捡起来，但它。
Claws weak as fuck.
爪子软到不行。
Aim for the head.
瞄准头部。
I can't answer that.
我无法回答。
It only lets me go like, halfway.
它只会让我走一半。
It doesn't like let me go push to the back.
它不喜欢让我推到后面。
Aim for the tail.
瞄准尾巴。
And for the tail. Oh.
而对于尾巴。 哦。
But no, that doesn't.
但不，那不是。
Make sense, does it? Hold on, wait. Hold on, hold on, hold on.
有道理，是吗？ 等等，等等。 坚持，坚持，坚持。
You might be onto something
你可能正在做某事
I don't know.
我不知道。
I could.
我可以。
OK, ok. OK, ok, ok. OK, let's look at this.
好的好的。 好好好。 好的，让我们看看这个。
Like maybe we should aim for like, back here.
喜欢也许我们应该瞄准喜欢，回到这里。
Like we could get it stuck on the legs or something.
就像我们可以把它卡在腿上什么的。
Why are you so fat?
你怎么这么胖？
Do realise the dog goes so fat?
你知道狗这么胖吗？
I thought I can't.
我以为我不能。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Is this possible?
这可能吗？
It's too heavy.
它太重了。
Yeah, the dog's too heavy, man.
是的，狗太重了，伙计。
I can't get on
我上不去
silencing saying I'm doing something wrong way.
沉默说我做错了事。
Am I doing something wrong, huh?
我做错什么了吧？
Don't grab push I'm.
不要抢推我。
I don't know how to push or a I like, move it
我不知道怎么推还是一个我喜欢的，把它移到家的一边。
I had to, like,
我不得不，就像，用爪子把它推开
perfectly.
完美。
One to
一到
help.
帮助。
It's not too late.
这还不算太晚。
A lower down a bit.
再低一点。
So it's not like it's you blaring in your ears.
因此，这不像是你在耳边咆哮。
OK, ok. Yeah, the dog.
好的好的。 是的，狗。
OK on a diet after I get them, this dog is going on a diet
好的，我得到它们后节食，这只狗正在节食
it's like, um, maybe.
就像，嗯，也许。
Maybe if I, if I go.
也许如果我，如果我去。
So far over here and then like, make it push.
到目前为止，然后喜欢，让它推动。
So the
所以
on, I'm going to try something.
上，我要试试看。
I don't know. I don't do I don't know this come on.
我不知道。 我不这样做我不知道这个来吧。
Quite like that.
就是这样。
And then
进而
is it like that? Like that. Far?
是这样吗？ 像那样。 远的？
What do you guys think.
你们有什么感想。
Push from the head?
从头顶推？
I don't know what you mean.
我不知道你想表达什么意思。
Push from the head.
从头部推。
Please.
请。
Oh, you're so fat.
哦，你太胖了。
It doesn't work.
它不起作用。
On raw
生的
all it can't even move like the
它甚至不能移动，就像爪子几乎没有移动一样。 他
pinch the tail.
捏尾巴。
I don't think I can pinch the tail.
我不认为我可以捏尾巴。
Can I have claws really weak? Ah.
我的爪子真的很弱吗？ 啊。
What if you use the claw to push it to the side.
如果你用爪子把它推到一边怎么办。
That's what I was trying to do.
这就是我想要做的。
I was trying to use the claw to push it.
我试图用爪子推动它。
So the so the right. Vise not doing that.
所以是对的。 虎钳不这样做。
So it's a scale. What do you.
所以它是一个尺度。 你是什​​么。
Mean it's a scale?
意思是秤？
I want my dog
我想要我的狗
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Can I get help? Is there a way for me to get help?
我能得到帮助吗？ 有没有办法让我得到帮助？
Free gifts.
免费赠品。
Acquisition judgement requests.
收购判断请求。
What does that mean?
这意味着什么？
Do you think somebody will help me
你认为有人会帮助我吗
pull from the front?
从前面拉？
I can't pull from the front.
我不能从前面拉。
It doesn't let me pull from the front.
它不允许我从前面拉。
It's impossible. It won't let me.
是不可能的。 它不会让我。
Yeah, it's like I.
是的，和我一样。
I want to go back further, but
我想回到更远的地方，但是
oh, where do I go?
哦，我要去哪里？
I don't know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办。
I maybe.
我可能是。
Hold on, hold on, hold on. Let me try something.
坚持，坚持，坚持。 让我试试看。
I could but I don't know.
我可以，但我不知道。
I don't.
我不。
Know what I'm trying to do, but we're trying to do something.
知道我想要做什么，但我们正在尝试做某事。
Oh, the why?
哦，为什么？
I thought maybe.
我想也许吧。
Maybe it's, like, I got to, like, cause like, you know how the centre.
也许是，就像，我必须，像，因为像，你知道中心是怎么回事。
Of gravity is?
重力是什么？
Like, he's the fattest, and maybe I should go
就像，他是最胖的，也许我应该去找他最薄弱的部分，试着把它推到那里，对吧？
Or, I don't know, physics.
或者，我不知道，物理学。
I was close.
我很接近。
Was it really close? I don't know.
真的很近吗？ 我不知道。
Go less forward, OK?
少往前走，好吗？
OK. Push it when you push this side, OK?
好的。 推这边的时候推一下，好吗？
All right, I'll listen. I'll listen to you.
好吧，我会听的。 我会听你的。
You seem to be an expert on this, so.
你似乎是这方面的专家，所以。
I kind.
我善良。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Yeah.
是的。
I like that.
我喜欢。
It's it's cheesy.
它是俗气的。
Guys, guys, it's g g. I can't.
伙计们，伙计们，这是gg。 我不能。
I can't do it all. I got it.
我做不到这一切。 我得到了它。
I can't do it, man. He's not budging.
我做不到，伙计。 他没有让步。
His voice are budging.
他的声音在颤抖。
Oh, is the other claw?
哦，是另一只爪子吗？
What do you mean, the other claw?
另一个爪子是什么意思？
Use the other claw like that one.
像那样使用另一只爪子。
Right here on the on the right.
就在这里，在右边。
Are oh, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold. On.
是哦，坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持。 在。
You might. You might be onto something.
你可能会。 你可能正在做某事。
You might be onto something. I didn't try this yet.
你可能正在做某事。 我还没试过这个。
So put.
这么说吧。
Like this.
像这样。
Your butt is so fucking thick.
你的屁股真他妈厚。
I don't know what to do, man.
我不知道该怎么办，伙计。
I can't go for the head, guys. I've tried it.
伙计们，我不能去抓头。 我试过了。
It doesn't want me go further back.
它不想让我再往前走。
Mm this is like a look.
嗯，这就像一个样子。
Like more than half of.
喜欢过半。
His body is stuck on top of the on
他的身体被困在平台的顶部。
I want him.
我要他。
As too heavy, man.
太重了，伙计。
Yeah, this is. This boy's too heavy.
是的，这是。 这小子太重了
I think we can
我想我们可以
we're.
是。
I don't know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办。
In. Pushing it from the middle.
在。 从中间推。
I don't think pushing.
我不认为推。
It from a mill is going to help. Is really chunky.
它来自工厂会有所帮助。 真的很厚实。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
I'll do one more.
我会再做一个。
I'll do one more. OK, just one more. Just just.
我会再做一个。 好的，就再来一张。 只是而已。
One more.
多一个。
Just one more.
还有一个。
Me. I can't.
我。 我不能。
I can't do it, guys.
我做不到，伙计们。
It's not it's not working.
不是它不工作。
It's not working.
它不工作。
Uh, it's stuck.
嗯，卡住了。
Call for help.
寻求帮助。
How do I call for help?
我该如何寻求帮助？
Help! Help!
帮助！ 帮助！
Oh, is. This button right here?
哦，是。 这个按钮在这里？
Is I press this button
我按下这个按钮了吗
or someone come and help me.
或者有人来帮助我。
If I press this button,
如果我按下这个按钮，
as this.
像这样。
I'm not sure.
我不确定。
Now. No, I can't call for.
现在。 不，我不能要求。
Oh, God, no.
哦，天哪，不。
OK. Mm.
好的。 毫米。
Oh, I guess I just got.
哦，我想我刚刚得到。
I just got to do your thing, bro.
我只是要做你的事，兄弟。
OK. OK, let's look.
好的。 好的，让我们看看。
Let's look around.
让我们环顾四周。
Let's look around. Are
让我们环顾四周。 是
I'm going to try one more time.
我要再试一次。
I'm gonna try.
我要试试。
OK, just one more.
好的，就再来一张。
Just one more. Just one more.
还有一个。 还有一个。
I want to see if I can you know,
我想看看能不能知道
move his butt a little bit to the to the right
将他的屁股向右移动一点
click, ok? OK.
点击，好吗？ 好的。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
OK. You know, I it's fine.
好的。 你知道，我很好。
It's fine. Did
没事。 做过
it won't let me go to the head?
它不会让我去头部吗？
I can't reach the head.
我够不到头。
Guys, I don't think you understand.
伙计们，我认为你不明白。
It won't let me go far back to get to the head
它不会让我走太远才能到达头部
push it down by poking it by.
戳它向下推。
Poking him normal.
戳他正常。
Poke him by doesn't let me.
戳他不让我。
Really push him down that much.
真的把他压低了那么多。
You know I haven't tried that.
你知道我没试过。
Have I.
我有没有。
Like like pushing down on the.
就像往下推一样。
Mm. I don't know it it's really hard to.
毫米。 我不知道这真的很难。
Push down on it though since he's so big
推倒它，因为他这么大
yeah. The dog's too fat.
是的。 狗太肥了
OK, all right.
好的没问题。
We'll come back to this, ok?
我们会回到这个，好吗？
If anybody look well, if anybody gets this one gone,
如果有人看起来不错，如果有人把这个弄丢了，
I'm going to be sad if there are people that.
如果有人那样，我会很难过。
You know, weaken it a bit.
你知道，削弱一点。
Hey, let me know, all right?
嘿，告诉我，好吗？
If you are. If you are. Ha, ha.
如果你是。 如果你是。 哈哈。
We kinda the thing. Like that more loose
我们有点像。 像这样更宽松
let me know
让我知道
I was in the middle of this now.
我现在正处于这中间。
I'm not going to continue.
我不打算继续了。
There might be better.
可能会有更好的。
What's it green games like around I.
我周围的绿色游戏是什么样的。
Always just.
永远只是。
Get rum right
正确选择朗姆酒
about the blue board.
关于蓝板。
I don't know, like, I can't do anything about that.
我不知道，就像，我对此无能为力。
It is.
这是。
I don't think it lets me do anything off the blue.
我不认为它让我做任何突然的事情。
Board.
木板。
It's impossible.
是不可能的。
You mean it's impossible?
你的意思是不可能？
Anything is possible if you put your mind to it, right?
只要下定决心，一切皆有可能，对吧？
I mean, that's what people say.
我的意思是，这就是人们所说的。
Which is journey.
这就是旅程。
Uh, there's a lot of round figurines.
呃，有很多圆形小雕像。
Are there so many rum figurines
有这么多朗姆酒小雕像吗
oh, this is possible.
哦，这是可能的。
Is this one possible?
这可能吗？
What do you guys think?
你们有什么感想？
Is this one?
这是一个吗？
Oh, we could do this. We could do this. Yeah.
哦，我们可以这样做。 我们可以做到这一点。 是的。
Yeah, it looks. It looks possible.
是的，看起来。 看起来有可能。
What do you mean? It's not possible?
你什么意思？ 这不可能？
You don't think so?
你不这么认为？
You just got to push it, right?
你只需要推动它，对吧？
He's got to push it until falls.
他必须推动它直到跌倒。
I think it doesn't look possible.
我认为这看起来不可能。
Well, you know what?
嗯，你知道吗？
We won't know until we try.
在我们尝试之前，我们不会知道。
Waiting for reservation.
等待预订。
Always somebody else playing already
总是有人在玩
oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Somebody is already playing.
已经有人在玩了。
Sorry.
对不起。
OK, I want to watch his technique, and we'll see what he does. Bro.
好的，我想看看他的技术，我们会看看他做了什么。 兄弟。
Oh, look at that.
哦，看那个。
Look at that. It just moves, like, ever so slightly.
看那个。 它只是移动，就像，非常轻微。
Is that the goal? You just got. To, like. Move it a bit.
那是目标吗？ 你刚得到。 喜欢。 稍微动一下。
Until he falls down huh?
直到他倒下是吧？
It's not that easy. Hmm.
这并不容易。 唔。
Hold on, hold on.
等一下，等一下。
There's there's other ones still.
还有其他的。
There's, like, there's more I can try.
还有，就像，我可以尝试更多。
Like, there's multiple rooms, and I'm not sure why
就像，有多个房间，我不知道为什么
yeah, there's one right here.
是的，这里有一个。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
What is this? Is it the same thing?
这是什么？ 是一样的吗？
I think it's the same thing.
我认为这是同一件事。
What's the ball game?
什么是球赛？
All No, wait.
不，等等。
Alan, hold on, hold on, hold on.
艾伦，等一下，等一下，等一下。
Wait. I'm good at these
等待。 我擅长这些
I. Think I can do it.
我认为我可以做到。
It's.
它的。
Yeah, it just has to get into the hole, right?
是的，它只需要进入洞，对吧？
I'm good at putting things in holes.
我擅长把东西放进洞里。
Watch this.
看这个。
Just gimme, gimme, gimme.
给我，给我，给我。
Like three balls. 12.
就像三个球一样。  12.
It's even grab a ball.
它甚至是抢球。
It didn't even grab a single ball. Huh?
它甚至没有抓住一个球。 嗯？
What is. That?
什么是。 那？
No balls.
没有球。
Yeah, I got no balls.
是的，我没有球。
Oh, my God. What
我的天啊。 什么
I just.
我只是。
Oh. OK.
哦。 好的。
Blue balled.
蓝球。
Shut up.
住口。
Hey, hey, you shut up! Shut up! No!
喂喂，你闭嘴！ 住口！ 不！
Oh, boy.
好家伙。
OK. OK.
好的。 好的。
Maybe maybe if I go a little bit more.
也许如果我多走一点。
On the like.
上之类的。
Could
可以
it's is it going to is going to cutting again?
是不是又要砍了？
Please don't cut me.
请不要剪我。
Please don't kill me. Grab a ball, grab a ball. Just grab one
请不要杀我。 抢球，抢球。 随便抓一个
of them.
其中。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的。
In the middle, in the middle. Right in the middle.
在中间，在中间。 就在中间。
Just drop it right in the middle.
把它放在中间就行了。
What is that?
那是什么？
What the fuck is that?
那是什么鬼？
It ain't even going to any of the holes.
它甚至不会进入任何一个洞。
Think even go to any of the holes.
想想甚至去任何一个洞。
Bro. Roar.
兄弟。 怒吼。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
What is happening?
怎么了？
OK, ok.
好的好的。
Well, it's good to know that there's multiple options though.
好吧，很高兴知道有多种选择。
OK, um.
好的，嗯。
All of these are rigged.
所有这些都是被操纵的。
So many of these are rigged down
其中很多都被操纵了
on what?
什么？
What what about this one? What's that? This one?
这个呢？ 那是什么？ 这个？
Same thing.
一样。
What is going on here?
这里发生了什么？
What is this?
这是什么？
Why is it just, like, shaking?
为什么只是，就像，在颤抖？
Oh, does he have to push it?
哦，他必须推吗？
Is he trying to push the
他是想推墙吗？ 坚持，稍等。
Yeah, I had to push it down to looks like.
是的，我不得不把它推到看起来像。
Is this on hard what do you guys think?
大佬们觉得这个难度大吗？
Is this one possible?
这可能吗？
Should I do this one?
我应该做这个吗？
I've never seen.
我从来没见过。
That.
那。
Yeah, I've never this is the first. Time I've ever seen this one.
是的，我从来没有这是第一次。 我见过这个的时间。
As long as. Impossible on the whole.
只要。 整体上是不可能的。
I don't know
我不知道
it's glued it to the
它被粘在有人说它粘在绳子上。
Is it really
真的吗
all the person that was on this just gave up?
所有的人都放弃了？
I think he left
我想他离开了
all air.
所有的空气。
Use my thingy.
用我的东西。
OK, it's too late. I guess I got a start, right?
好吧，为时已晚。 我想我有一个开始，对吧？
I guess I just got to start.
我想我得开始了。
This might be ok.
这可能没问题。
OK, well, we'll see.
好的，我们拭目以待。
We'll see about that.
我们会看到的。
I could.
我可以。
Oh, fuck me.
哦，操我。
I fucked up. I fucked up. I fucked up.
我搞砸了。 我搞砸了。 我搞砸了。
I fucked up. I fucked up.
我搞砸了。 我搞砸了。
Or did I. Or did I. What
还是我。还是我。什么
Excluded.
排除。
Excluded. Do you see that?
排除。 你看到了吗？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
There's no way that has to.
没有办法。
Be, like, glued or, like, taped to the string.
像胶水一样粘在绳子上。
No, no.
不，不。
Oh, my. God.
天啊。 上帝。
OK, this one's a scam.
好吧，这是一个骗局。
This one is 100% big, big scam.
这是100％的大骗局。
No, no, no, I'm not doing that.
不，不，不，我不会那样做。
Get me out
让我出去
what about this?
那这个呢？
What do I have to do for this one?
我该怎么办？
Is there, like, is it like picking up?
有没有，像，像捡起来一样吗？
What?
什么？
Yeah. What is this. One?
是的。 这是什么。 一？
I don't understand, because don't explain
我不明白，因为不解释
show me the card out.
把卡给我看看。
I to show me the card out.
我把卡给我看。
How do you hold on. Let's watch.
你怎么坚持。 让我们来看吧。
Let's watch this person try and do it.
让我们看这个人尝试去做。
Maybe I'll understand after watching them
也许我看了他们之后会明白我在看什么？
What's that doesn't look.
那是什么不看起来。
That doesn't look good.
那看起来不太好。
No, no, no, no.
不不不不。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
OK, I'm going to go back to go back to the regular one.
好的，我要回去回到普通的。
I see what's happening here.
我看到这里发生了什么。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
The guy gave up. The guy give up.
那家伙放弃了。 男主放弃。
The guy gave up. OK, ok. It's possible.
那家伙放弃了。 好的好的。 有可能的。
I think. I think I can.
我认为。 我觉得我可以。
I can grab it right? I just got it.
我能抢到吗？ 我刚得到它。
I just got move it. Slightly more slightly.
我刚搬过来 稍微多一点。
It's going to take a few tries.
这需要几次尝试。
I think I could do this one.
我想我可以做到这一点。
Right, right.
是的是的。
Right.
对。
Yeah.
是的。
I think they.
我觉得他们。
Loosened it up for me to like, hey,
松开它让我喜欢，嘿，
OK, let's try.
好的，我们试试。
Yeah, we can try. Yeah.
是的，我们可以试试。 是的。
I'll put
我会放
oh, that's a much
哦，那是很多
they do it right
他们做对了
oh, ok. OK.
哦好的。 好的。
Oh, it's looking.
哦，它正在寻找。
It's looking pretty good.
它看起来不错。
It's moving.
它在移动。
That's progress, right? There's there's progress. There.
这就是进步，对吧？ 有进步。 那里。
It's moving. Grab the head
它在移动。 抓住头
like back here.
就像回到这里。
Can I even go that far back
我还能走那么远吗
OK. All right, we'll try.
好的。 好吧，我们会努力的。
We'll try
我们会尽力的
oh, no, wait.
哦，不，等等。
I might not be far further enough.
我可能还不够远。
Oh, it is.
哦，是的。
It is.
这是。
What?
什么？
What is it heavier there or something?
那里的东西更重还是什么？
What am I missing? Something there? What?
我错过了什么？ 有什么吗？ 什么？
It didn't even move like it got budge.
它甚至一动也不动，好像有让步一样。
Just slightly.
只是轻微的。
I miss.
我想。
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
I miss it.
我想念它。
Like it didn't even push it
就像它甚至没有推动它一样
oh, it's too further.
哦，太远了。
I really miss old. I really miss.
真的很怀念老 我真的很想念。
I don't. Know. Oops.
我不。 知道。 哎呀。
It's not glued.
它没有粘合。
I don't think Zone's glued OK.
我不认为Zone粘好。
I guess I'll just stick to. My.
我想我会坚持下去。 我的。
I'll stick to this side instead.
我会坚持这一边。
Because on.
因为开。
Balance, it doesn't.
平衡，它没有。
Look too.
也看。
Whoa, whoa.
哇，哇。
That's good.
那很好。
That's really good.
那真的很好。
That was really good. OK, ok.
那真是太好了。 好的好的。
Got a lot of movement.
有很大的动静。
Off that one. Holy shit.
关闭那个。 天啊。
I think we can do it.
我认为我们可以做到。
I wish I had my heart.
我希望我有我的心。
And literally. Now.
从字面上看。 现在。
It's like I feel like my heart's like 150.
就像我觉得我的心像150。
She's
她是
on. I mean, look.
在。 我的意思是，看。
That's a to take a better look at it, I can't move it from here.
那是为了更好地看看它，我不能从这里移开它。
I mean, I probably could buy, like, I failed big time trying to do
我的意思是，我可能可以购买，比如，我在尝试这样做时失败了。
Spooky crankiness.
诡异的暴躁。
So spooky.
好诡异。
All right,
好的，
OK. All right, all right.
好的。 好吧，好吧。
It's it's still good. It's still good.
它仍然是好的。 它仍然很好。
We're moving it.
我们正在移动它。
We're moving it, man.
我们正在移动它，伙计。
Right?
对？
Yeah. Grab the middle.
是的。 抓住中间。
Grab the middle. I don't think.
抓住中间。 我不这样认为。
I think it's too heavy.
我觉得太重了。
Like, if I try to grab the.
就像，如果我试图抓住。
Middle, it's not even going to pick it up.
中间，它甚至不会捡起来。
Now, we're really close not them at all.
现在，我们真的很亲近，根本不是他们。
We can't grab them.
我们不能抓住他们。
Then all we had to go for the the weak spot.
然后我们必须去寻找弱点。
That's a yeah. Get the get the weak spot.
是的。 抓住弱点。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
There's people waiting right now.
现在有人在等。
They want to do like they're like vultures.
他们想像秃鹰一样做事。
You guys are vultures. All of you.
你们是秃鹰 你们所有人。
All five of you are vultures.
你们五个都是秃鹰。
I mean, I'm on the same cell
我的意思是，我在同一个牢房里
but. Chi Chi Chi Chi Chi. OK,
但。 咻咻咻咻咻。 好的，
let me see what
让我看看什么
maybe they'll push it even more if.
也许他们会更加努力。
I let go a few moments later,
片刻之后我放开了，
it moves a bit more
它移动得更多
there is a little bit more guys.
还有一点点的家伙。
A little bit more.
多一点点。
Right?
对？
Oh, God, dude, where do I go now?
哦，上帝，伙计，我现在要去哪里？
I want to try for the this.
我想试试这个。
Part again by I don't know
再分开我不知道
try the right corner.
试试右边的角落。
I'm going to try to go for the back again, maybe.
也许我会尝试再次回到后面。
Yeah.
是的。
This seems like seems like a good lesson.
这似乎是一个很好的教训。
We did it.
我们做到了。
Oh wow.
哇哦。
I there might be a weaker.
我可能有一个较弱的。
Now though since I moved this a bit.
现在虽然我移动了一点。
OK, ok, let's just try let's just try
好的，好的，让我们试试吧，让我们试试吧
it. OK?
它。 好的？
Potters
陶工
joggers.
慢跑者。
What.
什么。
I don't think I don't think I'm going to get anything by.
我不认为我不认为我会得到任何东西。
Moving it back there.
把它移回那里。
That looks so dumb.
这看起来太傻了。
Oh, so dumb.
哦，太笨了。
I can't do that. I got six of.
我不能那样做。 我得到了六个。
The the backs, the the bottom part of the
背面，盒子的底部右侧。
It's all for sure.
这一切都是肯定的。
Yeah. I mean, that's. That's Korean games.
是的。 我的意思是，就是这样。 那就是韩国游戏。
Oh. Mm.
哦。 毫米。
Oh. Ok. OK.
哦。 行。 好的。
What I do.
我做什么。
What do I do, y'all.
我该怎么办，你们。
Bro, bro, bro.
兄弟，兄弟，兄弟。
What I do what I do what I do what I do
我做什么 我做什么 我做什么 我做什么
you can get this at the bottom.
你可以在底部得到这个。
Yeah, I think I just say at the bottom.
是的，我想我只是在底部说。
That seems like the only thing we can do right now.
这似乎是我们现在唯一能做的事情。
It's the thing that's working for us right
这是对我们有用的东西，对了。
Chi chi.
奇奇。
There's a little too much there.
那里有点太多了。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Again.
再次。
And moves just a little bit.
并且移动一点点。
It just moves only a little bit.
它只是移动了一点点。
Ah ha.
啊哈。
Go over the bottom edge.
越过底部边缘。
Like the very, very bottom edge.
就像非常非常底部的边缘。
Glossaryck roll the ones.
词汇表滚动那些。
The ones out.
出来的。
My arcade aren't nearly this week.
我的街机这周快不行了。
Mm mm.
嗯嗯。
We're going to the middle. Get me.
我们要去中间。 得到我。
I don't think it's.
我不认为它是。
Strong enough to, like, even do anything in the middle
足够强大，甚至可以在中间做任何事情
I feel like I'm going to.
我觉得我要去。
You're if you're telling me if I try to go for the middle
你是如果你告诉我如果我试着去中间
really try the middle.
真的试试中间。
I will keep saying try the middle.
我会一直说尝试中间。
I'm that scary. That is scary.
我就是那么可怕。 那是可怕的。
OK, I'll trust you.
好的，我会相信你的。
Chi Chi Chi Chi.
奇奇奇奇。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Well, I don't even know what happened.
好吧，我什至不知道发生了什么。
I don't even know what happened.
我什至不知道发生了什么。
What was that? Did it was that good guys?
那是什么？ 有那么好人吗？
Was that good?
那很好吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Don't those good was that a good thing or was a bad thing?
难道那些好事是好事还是坏事？
It just flipped. I mean, maybe that's good.
它只是翻转。 我的意思是，也许这很好。
All right.
好的。
Maybe that's good that we flipped it, huh?
也许我们翻转它是件好事，对吧？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Yeah, OK.
是的，好的。
The left claw is strong.
左爪很强壮。
Yeah, it was strong.
是的，它很强大。
Know they had change anything
知道他们改变了什么
mm OK.
毫米好的。
I'm going to try to get the edge again.
我将尝试再次获得优势。
Pull on. Try edging it one more time.
拉上。 尝试再磨边一次。
I'm really good at edging.
我真的很擅长磨边。
You know that
你知道的
hey, that's pretty good.
嘿，这还不错。
That's pretty good. It's getting closer.
这是相当不错的。 它越来越近了。
It's getting closer and closer.
它越来越近了。
So it's like, drop me inside.
就像，让我进去。
Please, please.
请，请。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I'm sure I try the middle again, but I don't know.
我确定我会再次尝试中间，但我不知道。
That seems kind of like it seem. Kind of.
这看起来有点像。 有点儿。
It seems scary because I feel like it might reset my.
这似乎很可怕，因为我觉得它可能会重置我的。
Progress if I try and do that.
如果我尝试这样做，就会取得进步。
I'll try the front again.
我会再试试前面的。
Try the front again.
再试试前面。
I don't think going for the front is a good idea because the
我不认为去前线是一个好主意，因为
the right claws weak as fuck.
右爪弱到他妈的。
Maybe like maybe like bottom middle right.
也许像右下角一样。
Point.
观点。
Like I'm I'm trying to abuse that the left claws
就像我一样，我试图滥用左爪更强壮
like right here.
就像在这里。
What if we do this
如果我们这样做怎么办
I fuck up.
我他妈的。
Oh, wait, whoa, whoa, whoa.
哦，等等，哇，哇，哇。
I just got. To push it in. I just got to push it in now, right?
我刚得到。 把它推进去。我现在就得把它推进去，对吧？
Is that is that how it works?
这就是它的工作原理吗？
I think
我认为
I think that's good. I just got to push it.
我认为这很好。 我只好推它。
Only I just I'll push it.
只有我只是我会推动它。
Or maybe I lift up the back
或者也许我抬起背部
or maybe I lift off the back part like
或者我可能会像
I think I think if I try and lift up the back.
我想我想如果我试着抬起背部。
Part, it will like fall in right.
部分，它会喜欢落入正确的。
Per head. Yeah, we go for that.
每头。 是的，我们为此而努力。
We go for that.
我们为此而努力。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Oh, I got all no mods. Can we get a pole.
哦，我没有任何模组。 我们能不能拿一根杆子。
Can we get a pole as I go for the head or do I go for the.
我们可以在我去头部的时候得到一根杆子还是我去。
Bottom part like.
底部像。
So I try and push it in. Or do I try and lift it up.
所以我试着把它推进去。或者我试着把它举起来。
I don't know what's a good option.
我不知道什么是好的选择。
Here by pushing it or lifting from the lifting from the head
在这里通过推它或从头部抬起或推底部
as I'm sure
我敢肯定那些是其他人会知道的。
I don't know
我不知道
all a lot of OK,
一切都很好，很多人都说现在就去争取。
A lot of people say go for the head, OK.
很多人都说去打头，OK。
Head, head.
头，头。
So no head.
所以没有头。
OK. OK, we're going for the head.
好的。 好的，我们要去头了。
We're going for that.
我们正在为此而努力。
Cut one.
剪一个。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, you're such a cock teaser.
哦，你真是个公鸡挑逗者。
What the fuck was I? It's
我他妈是什么？ 它是
all raw.
都是生的。
Oh, my God. My adrenaline.
我的天啊。 我的肾上腺素。
My adrenaline.
我的肾上腺素。
It's so close.
它是如此接近。
Yeah, it is getting super fucking close.
是的，它变得超级他妈的接近。
It's right there.
它就在那里。
It's just sitting there.
它只是坐在那里。
Oh, I'll
哦，我会
try again.
再试一次。
Yeah, I'm definitely going for that.
是的，我肯定会这样做。
I just don't know if I should go, like, more inner closer to the middle.
我只是不知道我是否应该去，喜欢，更靠近中间。
Maybe I.
也许我。
Could. OK.
可以。 好的。
OK, right there.
好的，就在那儿。
Like, maybe right there.
就像，也许就在那儿。
What the heck?
有没有搞错？
A bra
胸罩
lights.
灯。
It didn't. Move.
它没有。 移动。
It did move at all.
它确实移动了。
So just try the bottom.
所以就试试底部吧。
Oh, my God. I don't know.
我的天啊。 我不知道。
I just try the bottom at this point.
我只是在这一点上尝试底部。
Do the people watching must be like, no.
看的人一定是这样的，没有。
Do this, do that.
做这个，做那个。
But I follow.
但我跟着。
Guys like, I'm fucking up.
伙计们喜欢，我他妈的。
OK, I'll do the bottom. Just once.
好的，我会做底部的。 就一次。
I'm like, I tried just once.
我喜欢，我只试过一次。
Just once
就一次
and see what happens. Come
看看会发生什么。 来
I didn't push it.
我没有推它。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
That's my bad.
那是我的错。
That's my bad. I, I fucked up.
那是我的错。 我，我搞砸了。
I think I got to be a little.
我想我得有点。
Bit more further to the to the right.
再往右边一点。
So too far. No, not too far.
太远了。 不，不会太远。
Not far. Enough. I think
不远。 足够。 我认为
ok. OK, let's. Try.
行。 好吧，让我们。 尝试。
Chi chi.
奇奇。
Chi chi chi.
咻咻咻。
Like that far.
就那么远。
So then the left clock in like, push it and maybe
那么左边的时钟就像，推它，也许
right.
对。
You see what I'm getting out? You see what I'm going?
你看到我在说什么了吗？ 你明白我要做什么了吗？
It doesn't work.
它不起作用。
It doesn't work, guys.
这行不通，伙计们。
Oh, no,
不好了，
I'm stumped, man.
我被难住了，伙计。
It's not strong enough to push it in.
它不够强大，无法将其推入。
I just got to stick to the hard gas.
我只需要坚持使用硬气。
Stick to the top.
坚持到顶部。
Yeah. Mm.
是的。 毫米。
Try lifting the left corner.
尝试抬起左角。
Uh, uh, uh,
嗯嗯嗯嗯
uh. Hold on.
呃。 坚持，稍等。
Let me try
让我尝试
let me see
让我看看
it's hot.
很热。
For what the fuck.
到底是为了什么。
Did I just, like, get?
我只是，喜欢，得到了吗？
I'm just like, fuck myself.
我就像，操我自己。
I don't know what happened there.
我不知道那里发生了什么。
Li. I don't know what happened there.
李。 我不知道那里发生了什么。
I ruined it.
我毁了它。
I don't think I ruined it.
我不认为我毁了它。
Did I it went back. Should out.
难道我回去了。 应该出。
I don't know how
我不知道怎么
I fucked solve.
我他妈的解决了。
I know I'm fucked up how, how how I fuck
我知道我是怎么搞砸的，我是怎么搞砸爱的。
Me motion no.
我的动议没有。
Damn it, it might be good it might be good.
该死的，它可能是好的，它可能是好的。
How how that might be good.
怎么可能好。
Oh, maybe it is good.
哦，也许这很好。
Oh, maybe you're right. Maybe you have a point there.
哦，也许你是对的。 也许你有一个观点。
Maybe you have a point
也许你有道理
I can push.
我可以推。
Yeah, push the bottom again.
是的，再次推底。
Maybe it's.
也许是。
Maybe I saved it.
也许我保存了它。
Yeah, maybe I saved it.
是的，也许我保存了它。
I could.
我可以。
Ooh. It's for
哦。 那是为了
me. Oh.
我。 哦。
Boy. Oh, bra roll around.
男生。 哦，胸罩滚来滚去。
Oh, I fucked it up again.
哦，我又搞砸了。
It's so I keep I keep messing it up.
所以我一直在搞砸。
Oh, now it's back, baby.
哦，现在它回来了，宝贝。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
It's back to how it was before
它回到了以前的样子
on Niall.
关于尼尔。
Yeah, this O'Neil moment.
是的，这个奥尼尔时刻。
O'Neil moment.
奥尼尔时刻。
Let me try and.
让我试试看。
Cut. Look, I'm. Bring it back.
切。 看，我是 把它带回来。
Bring back again.
再带回来。
All will happen, will happen.
一切都会发生，都会发生。
However, it's over.
然而，一切都结束了。
What do you mean it's over?
结束了是什么意思？
It's not over.
它还没有结束。
All don't play.
都不会玩。
I'm too far.
我太远了。
Guys, guys, I'm too far into this to stop now.
伙计们，伙计们，我现在太过分了，不能停下来。
There's five people waiting because they know they can get it.
有五个人在等待，因为他们知道他们可以得到它。
I can't just give up right now.
我不能现在就放弃。
If I give up right now, then.
如果我现在放弃，那么。
Then I'm it's g g i i
那我就是 g g i i
i can't give. Up right now.
我不能给。 马上起来。
If I try and push the life again.
如果我再次尝试推动生活。
Suck suck
吸吮你的鸡巴
please.
请。
It's not budging all it doesn't budge anymore
它没有让步，它不再让步，因为它就像它仍然被卡在杆子上一样。
I can't do that anymore, guys.
我不能再这样做了，伙计们。
People keep saying, trying.
人们一直在说，在努力。
To go for the middle
去中间
and think going for the middle is good, isn't
并认为走中间是好的，不是吗
going for the middle?
去中间？
Are you sure? Pride?
你确定吗？ 自豪？
Are you sure? Huh?
你确定吗？ 嗯？
You're a liar.
你是个骗子。
It froze
它冻结了
all. What?
全部。 什么？
That was weird.
那很奇怪。
I thought it broke. For a second.
我以为它坏了。 一秒钟。
Yeah. Huh?
是的。 嗯？
What happened?
发生了什么？
Oh, come on, Ma, can you come help me?
哦，来吧，妈，你能来帮帮我吗？
God, God, are you there?
上帝，上帝，你在吗？
Please, please come help help me.
拜托，请过来帮帮我。
I don't know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办。
I'm like, the only.
我就像，唯一的。
Thing I can see trying to do
我可以看到尝试做的事情就是把电视放在中间没有任何帮助，兄弟。
Uh, baa, baa.
嗯，咩咩。
Baa, baa. Cut.
呸呸呸。 切。
All of that stuff.
所有这些东西。
Far, far enough.
远，够远。
Oh, god.
天啊。
Please.
请。
Oh, God, please.
哦，上帝，请。
Wow. Oh, my God.
哇。 我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, God.
天啊。
It did something.
它做了一些事情。
It did something that was pretty good.
它做了一些非常好的事情。
It was pretty good. It was pretty good. Guys,
这是相当不错的。 这是相当不错的。 伙计们，
there's there's so much happening
发生了这么多事情，这个他妈的盒子发生了这么多事情，伙计。
Now I can grab the bottom.
现在我可以抓住底部了。
I can grab the bottom now, right?
我现在可以抓住底部了，对吧？
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
What the fuck is this?
这是什么鬼？
How's it look on the side.
侧面看怎么样。
We've made
不过，我们在这个愚蠢的盒子上取得了很大进展。
Put OK.
放好。
I think that's enough.
我认为这就足够了。
We'll see.
我们拭目以待。
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
哦，哇，哇，哇。
Whoa, whoa, whoa. That's massive.
哇，哇，哇。 那是巨大的。
That is massive.
那是巨大的。
Cock in my arse.
公鸡在我的屁股上。
Dude, what's like.
哥们，什么情况。
This is this is really. Looking good.
这是真的。 看起来不错。
It's looking great.
它看起来很棒。
Is looking amazing right now.
现在看起来很神奇。
De la la.
德拉拉。
I think we can get it.
我想我们可以得到它。
I'm pretty sure we can get it right.
我很确定我们可以做对。
It's you're all all I got.
你就是我的全部。
I don't have to scream for it's only 4 hours.
我不必尖叫，因为它只有 4 个小时。
Before it's time for our.
在它是我们的时间之前。
Crew. Cut
全体人员。 切
OK. I think that's it.
好的。 我想就是这样。
I think.
我认为。
I think. Wow.
我认为。 哇。
Hey, why does he keep teasing.
嘿嘿，他怎么老是开玩笑。
Me like this?
我这样？
Well.
好。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
We're so close. We're so fucking close.
我们是如此接近。 我们太他妈亲密了。
We're so close. Dude, look at it.
我们是如此接近。 哥们，看看吧。
Look at it.
看它。
Why this looks so dumb, by the way.
顺便说一句，为什么这看起来如此愚蠢。
Yeah, just.
是的，只是。
Oh, just.
哦，只是。
One more thing. Just one more.
还有一件事。 还有一个。
How have we do prediction for that?
我们如何对此进行预测？
Oh, we know there's already production going on man.
哦，我们知道已经开始生产了。
OK, is that enough?
好的，够了吗？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Just moved.
刚搬家。
It moved like a tiny chub.
它像一个小鲢鱼一样移动。
So I.
所以我。
Swear, it's the inside.
发誓，这是内部。
It's all just one.
这只是一个。
More.
更多的。
It's going to be like five more.
它会像另外五个。
Something
某物
it's so close.
它是如此接近。
Oh, my God, bro.
哦，天哪，兄弟。
It's so, so fucking close.
它是如此，如此他妈的接近。
I don't want to fuck up and, like, bring it back to, like.
我不想搞砸，喜欢，把它带回来，喜欢。
A position where it's impossible, you know,
一个不可能的位置，你知道，就像，这就是我
I'm going to choke.
我要窒息了。
I don't want to shock.
我不想震惊。
Chi Chi Chi Chi Chi.
咻咻咻咻咻。
All right, all right, all right.
好的，好的，好的。
Please, please.
请，请。
Oh, my God. Just go inside.
我的天啊。 就进去吧。
Just go inside.
就进去吧。
Please, please.
请，请。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Just go inside.
就进去吧。
Why is it not going in?
为什么进不去？
Oh, my God. What is in?
我的天啊。 里面有什么？
It's not going in.
它不进去。
Maybe it's more.
也许更多。
I can't believe I spent, like, almost.
我简直不敢相信我几乎花了。
This is, like, pretty much almost 100, but I don't know how much
这差不多是100，但我不知道有多少
this thing is actually worth.
这东西其实是值得的。
We're so close.
我们是如此接近。
Yeah, it's almost there.
是的，它几乎就在那里。
Answer. It's almost there.
回答。 它几乎就在那里。
I could.
我可以。
You. Know, we just got to keep them nudging
你。 知道，我们只需要让他们轻推
bit by bit.
逐步地。
Also too far.
也太远了。
What is that?
那是什么？
Emotional damage?
感情伤害？
Is. So it goes.
是。 就这样。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Measure.
措施。
Push it from this side. Know
从这边推。 知道
move the other side.
移动另一边。
Yeah, yeah. I think that's that's that's a good that's good call.
是啊是啊。 我认为这是一个很好的决定。
That's a really good call.
这是一个非常好的电话。
Only on.
只开。
OK, ok. OK,
好的好的。 好的，
hop OK.
跳好。
What's
什么是
all I'm going to go crazy.
我要疯了。
I'm gonna lose my fucking mind.
我他妈的要疯了。
What is what do I do now?
我现在该怎么办？
What do I do now?
现在我该怎么做？
Just push it, make.
只需推动它，制作。
It, push it in
推进去
shove it, just shove it.
推它，只是推它。
So just
所以就
f really
f 真的从中间抓住它或推它。
I don't know what to do, bro.
我不知道该怎么办，兄弟。
Oh. Oh. Now
哦。 哦。 现在
OK. All right. I'm
好的。 好的。 我是
just grab it from the middle.
只需从中间抓住它。
I feel like I'm going to lose all my progress
如果我这样做，我觉得我会失去所有的进步，但我们会看到的。
I want to fuck around, find out
我想他妈的，找出来
I want to see.
我想看看。
I want to fuck around and find out and see what happens.
我想到处乱逛，看看会发生什么。
Let's just see what happens.
让我们看看会发生什么。
It kind of almost worked
它几乎起作用了
oh, boy.
好家伙。
Push the corners. Really.
推角。 真的。
So just push the corners.
所以只是推角。
You know, you might have a point there, OK? Good.
你知道，你可能有一个观点，好吗？ 好的。
A good idea.
一个好主意。
Really good idea.
真是个好主意。
Just push the corners right
只需向右推角
oh, ah. Oh,
哦，啊。 哦，
what do I do?
我该怎么办？
Someone save me.
有人救我。
A soul and save me hell.
一个灵魂，救我下地狱。
That's all in hell
那都是地狱
I'm I'm I'm stuck.
我是我是我被卡住了。
Get a bit closer now.
现在靠近一点。
You. This is, this is so this is painful.
你。 这就是，这太痛苦了。
This is so painful.
这太痛苦了。
I don't know where to go yards here.
我不知道去哪里码这里。
I don't know which way to go from mm.
我不知道从哪里去mm。
Look at the front corner and try to hit the claw
看前角并尝试击中杠铃所在的爪子将其推入前角
and try to hit the claw where the bar is to push it in.
并尝试击中将杆推入的爪子。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
That that corner
那个角落
OK. Put.
好的。 放。
I'll trust you
我会相信你
what I did so far
到目前为止我所做的是否太过分了？
I think that was too far.
我认为那太远了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I look like a stupid idiot.
我看起来像个愚蠢的白痴。
I look so stupid
到目前为止，我看起来很愚蠢，输入滞后。
There's some there's some input lag.
有些输入滞后。
Guys, it's hard. I.
伙计们，这很难。 一世。
Mean, this is pain.
意思是，这很痛苦。
People in pickle always
泡菜的人总是
OK, well, that is hard enough.
好吧，好吧，这已经够难了。
No, it doesn't do. Oh.
不，不行。 哦。
What is this?
这是什么？
What does this?
这是做什么的？
Is this time?
是这个时候吗？
What's
什么是
I don't.
我不。
Please wait without quitting
请稍等不退出
someone coming to help?
有人来帮忙？
Someone come to help.
有人来帮忙。
Oh, my God. Am I. Is God coming?
我的天啊。 我是。上帝来了吗？
Oh, is God going to help me?
哦，上帝会帮助我吗？
Wait.
等待。
What? Huh?
什么？ 嗯？
What the fuck happened? God.
到底是怎么回事？ 上帝。
God, what did you do?
天哪，你做了什么？
Do I just put away?
我只是收起来吗？
Don't just push it. Oh, my God. Do I just push it?
不要只是推动它。 我的天啊。 我只是推它吗？
I just.
我只是。
I just push it in.
我只是推进去。
This is all I.
这就是我的全部。
Have to do.
必须做。
I'll think.
我会想。
I think I just push it in or that I lift it up from the back
我想我只是把它推进去或者我从后面把它举起来
of the head again.
再次的头部。
I can't believe.
我不敢相信。
I suck so bad that they had to help me too.
我太糟糕了，他们也不得不帮助我。
OK, thank you.
好的谢谢。
Whoever you are.
无论你是谁。
Thank you. Oh.
谢谢你。 哦。
How do I go for the back?
我怎么去后面？
Like, you know, back here?
就像，你知道，回到这里？
Do I lift up from the from.
我从那里抬起来。
The from where the the green stuff is or do I just push it
绿色的东西是从哪里来的，还是我只是推它
from from the air, from the top head
从空中，从头顶，从后面。
Not do it.
不做。
Maybe. Maybe we can.
也许。 也许我们可以。
Yeah. Let's try the back
是的。 让我们试试后面
we can.
我们可以。
Even golf that far back. Is my question.
甚至打高尔夫球那么远。 是我的问题。
Oh. I
哦。 一世
it's scary man.
这是一个可怕的人。
I don't want to fuck it up. I don't want to fuck up.
我不想搞砸了。 我不想搞砸了。
The only chance I think.
我认为唯一的机会。
They're going to give me right
他们会给我权利
pull it from the.
把它从里面拉出来。
Back. OK, ok, ok.
后退。 好好好。
Pull it from the back. Come
从后面拉。 来
oh, oh, god.
哦，哦，天哪。
Oh, oh,
哦，哦，
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
We got it now.
我们现在明白了。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Roll roar.
滚吼。
I'm going to come.
我要来了。
I'm going to. Oh.
我要去。 哦。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
I felt so good.
我感觉很好。
Like God down, man.
就像上帝一样，伙计。
Now it's ideal.
现在它是理想的。
I got it's all on
我知道了
do I just sit here
我只是坐在这里吗
like like what's up?
喜欢喜欢什么？
What do I do now?
现在我该怎么做？
I just sit here and wait or. Are
我只是坐在这里等待或。 是
is he going to claim the prise?
他要夺冠吗？
I don't know how to claim the prise. How do I claim the prise?
我不知道如何领奖。 我如何领取奖品？
Happens now?
现在发生？
I don't know what happens now.
我不知道现在会发生什么。
Exit out of it.
退出它。
OK, I got it now. All right.
好的，我现在明白了。 好的。
It's added to my cart.
它已添加到我的购物车。
Congratulations.
恭喜。
You want to re zero something?
你想重新归零吗？
OK. Wow.
好的。 哇。
That's awesome, bro.
这太棒了，兄弟。
Yeah, it's in my cart. POG.
是的，它在我的购物车里。  POG。
Oh, my god.
我的天啊。
We got it.
我们得到了它。
And I'm so happy. Oh.
我很高兴。 哦。
Oh, thank you.
哦谢谢。
Thank you, god for thank you, god for coming and saving my vote.
谢谢你，上帝感谢你，上帝来拯救我的选票。
When all seem that when everything seems like you know
当一切似乎当一切似乎你都知道
it's at a loss, I can I can always rely on on the
很茫然，我可以一直依靠
the man behind the camera who's watching
镜头后面的那个正在看的人
and wishing for my success I guess
我想希望我的成功
what if they're watching the stream right now?
如果他们现在正在观看直播怎么办？
Nah, there's no way.
不，没有办法。
There's no way. OK.
不可能。 好的。
Well, I mean, we got one.
好吧，我的意思是，我们有一个。
We got one
我们得到了一个
now. Do we go back to the toggle?
现在。 我们回到切换开关吗？
Yeah. Let me check on the dagger.
是的。 让我检查一下匕首。
Let's see how what he's up to.
让我们看看他是怎么做到的。
Hot. As this time.
热的。 和这次一样。
What do you mean, us this time.
你什么意思，我们这次。
Huh? What? No.
嗯？ 什么？ 不。
Get me in. There. Get me in there.
让我进去。那里。 让我进去。
Oh, no. How did they do this?
不好了。 他们是怎么做到的？
How did these. People do this?
这些是怎么做到的。 人们这样做？
Oh, what now?
哦，现在呢？
No, I'm too late. It's gone.
不，我来晚了。 它不见了。
I'm too late.
我来不及了。
So I'm just going to get it.
所以我只是要得到它。
Already is, guys.
已经是了，伙计们。
Because I saw Asa wait in line.
因为我看到阿萨在排队等候。
How did they do that?
他们是怎么做到的？
All lost somewhere here.
都在这里的某个地方迷路了。
The dog was, like, all the way pushed in why.
那条狗，就像，一直被推到为什么。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Y'all oh.
你们都哦。
The song.
这首歌。
Actually hold.
其实坚持。
With it.
用它。
OK, so the person that was assists.
好的，所以那个是助攻的人。
Oh, they got the got on.
哦，他们上车了。
God to come up and help, help the dog. OK.
上帝来帮助，帮助狗。 好的。
I mean, I can't see.
我的意思是，我看不到。
Anything right now.
现在什么都行。
I just have to sit here and wait
我只需要坐在这里等待，因为现在还有其他人在玩直到正确
yeah.
是的。
I can't see anything.
我什么都看不见。
I don't know. Maybe.
我不知道。 也许。
Maybe I can just like snake it out and chill here.
也许我可以像蛇一样在这里放松一下。
And so, like, they get bored and go.
所以，就像，他们觉得无聊就走了。
Maybe there's a chance.
也许有机会。
There's there's always a chance.
总有机会的。
Sorry.
对不起。
I got round.
我圆了。
Yeah, I got, I got room
是的，我有，我有房间
to my attitude about it.
我对它的态度。
OK. Yeah.
好的。 是的。
What is he doing right now? Come on, come on.
他现在在做什么？ 好啦好啦。
Hurry up.
赶快。
You know, there's five.
你知道，有五个。
People waiting right now.
人们现在在等待。
I am probably number five, so I don't think.
我可能排在第五位，所以我不认为。
God, I don't think I can do anything right now.
上帝，我不认为我现在可以做任何事情。
Until they're off, until they're done. Try.
直到他们离开，直到他们完成。 尝试。
I make a scream, baker, by the way, like, increase it a bit.
我发出一声尖叫，面包师，顺便说一下，增加一点。
Hold on. Like like
坚持，稍等。 喜欢喜欢
like make it this big.
喜欢让它这么大。
What do you guys think? Bigger.
你们有什么感想？ 大。
There's better
有更好的
belts.
腰带。
Better.
更好的。
Too much bigger is better.
越大越好。
OK, cool.
嗯不错。
Yeah.
是的。
Now you can see the whole thing, right?
现在你可以看到整个事情了，对吧？
It's a bit easier to see.
它更容易看到。
Yeah.
是的。
So, um, I don't know what's going on with this guy.
所以，嗯，我不知道这个人是怎么回事。
He's just kind of he's just kind of chillin.
他只是有点他只是有点冷。
I love how the dog it.
我怎么爱狗呢。
Looks like the dog's like, hanging on for dear life.
看起来像狗一样，为亲爱的生命而坚持。
Oh, thank you for the.
哦，谢谢你。
High train, by the way.
顺便说一句，高铁。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
I didn't really notice that. There a string.
我真的没有注意到这一点。 有一个字符串。
Thank you so much. My
非常感谢。 我的
I feel like what if what if the person what if the person here
我觉得如果这个人怎么样，如果这里的人像一个观众，他们就像，他们在取笑我，对吧？
You're cruel.
你很残忍。
You're cruel. Then if.
你很残忍。 那么如果。
Somebody is watching me right now.
现在有人在监视我。
And they're just, like, taunting me of the dog and you suck,
他们只是，就像，嘲笑我的狗，你很烂，
suck I don't think.
吸我不认为。
I don't think anyone's doing that, though. I doubt it.
不过，我认为没有人这样做。 我对此表示怀疑。
Oh, OK. Oh.
哦好的。 哦。
Well, in a second, what is happens my
好吧，等一下，我的会发生什么
I think I got karma.
我想我得到了因果报应。
I think I just got karma for spitting on you guys.
我想我只是因为向你们吐口水而受到了因果报应。
OK, now remind her back.
好的，现在提醒她回来。
No, oh, oh.
不，哦，哦。
I wanted it.
我想要它。
God damn it. Roll
他妈的。 卷
bye, dog.
再见，狗。
Oh, the dog is gone now.
哦，狗现在不见了。
They got the dog.
他们得到了狗。
I wanted the dog.
我想要那条狗。
All this.
这一切。
I know.
我知道。
It's possible
有可能的
it's OK.
没关系。
I got. I got. I got them.
我有。 我有。 我得到了他们。
I want the.
我想要。
Dog. The dog, though.
狗。 狗，不过。
Yeah.
是的。
I think I'm going to try and try for the dog.
我想我会为狗而努力。
I really want him.
我真的很想要他。
He's so cute, man.
他太可爱了，伙计。
This little big, fluffy fucker.
这个又大又毛茸茸的小混蛋。
You're expecting me not to try for him.
你指望我不要为他而努力。
I think they're.
我认为他们是。
Going to refill it soon with another dog. So
很快就会用另一只狗补充它。 所以
let's just wait.
让我们等着。
That's the way a bit and see a farm.
就是这样一点，看到一个农场。
They refill it.
他们补充它。
Please give me.
请给我。
I just want a dog.
我只想要一条狗。
Gimme, gimme, gimme
给我，给我，给我真实的。
Oh, oh. Oh,
哦，哦。 哦，
oh, I'm here.
哦，我在这里。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
I mean, now I
我的意思是，现在我什么，
are they going to put.
他们要放吗？
Another dog in a dog?
狗中的另一只狗？
Dog? All local, please.
狗？ 请所有本地人。
Please.
请。
Just start.
刚开始。
I don't know where to start.
我不知道从哪里开始。
I can't start until, like, there's a you know, there's something that's ill.
我不能开始，直到，就像，你知道，有什么病了。
There's no dog.
没有狗。
I'll put another one in.
我再放一个进去。
Come on, please.
来吧，拜托。
Yeah.
是的。
They got to find another dog to put inside there.
他们必须找到另一只狗放在里面。
Because they're already gotten.
因为他们已经得到了。
The what if they're adults?
如果他们是成年人怎么办？
Won't that be sad that they run our stock
他们经营我们的股票会不会很伤心
hello?
你好？
Hello.
你好。
Please,
请，
please.
请。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Yeah, we got away. They're going to make a sweet
是的，我们逃走了。 他们要做一个甜点
I don't know what it says.
我不知道它说的是什么。
Can somebody translate? What does that say?
有人可以翻译吗？ 那说明什么？
It's like maintenance or something.
这就像维护什么的。
Or like.
或者喜欢。
Yeah, they're, like, putting in a new dog. Go
是的，他们就像在养一只新狗。 去
it says limited dog doing.
它说有限的狗做。
Oh, it's limited. You're right.
哦，那是有限的。 你说的对。
It says it's limited up here. Fuck me, bro.
它说这里是有限的。 操我，兄弟。
No, we have to get one done.
不，我们必须完成一项工作。
OK? OK.
好的？ 好的。
I mean, I see a suckers.
我的意思是，我看到一个吸盘。
No, this is.
不，这是。
Harder.
更难。
Oh, this is harder, bro.
哦，这更难，兄弟。
Oh, no,
不好了，
I don't think we're going to get this one.
我不认为我们会得到这个。
I don't know how.
我不知道怎么。
I don't know what I'm. What am I supposed to do here?
我不知道我是什么。 我应该在这里做什么？
What's what's our what's our game plan to try and get the dog
我们的目标是什么 我们的游戏计划是什么
yeah.
是的。
This one.
这个。
This one looks so hard
这个看起来好难
push the bite.
推动咬合。
What?
什么？
What if we just push the bite?
如果我们只是推动咬合呢？
Yeah, you're right.
是的，没错。
What if we just push the button a little bit?
如果我们只是按一下按钮呢？
Put I'm dumb, I'm stupid, I'm stupid.
说我笨，我笨，我笨。
I'm so stupid. OK, no, that that's work.
我太傻了。 好的，不，那是工作。
That's a another
那是另一个
hold on.
坚持，稍等。
What if I.
如果我。
I don't know which claw stronger the left one or the right one?
不知左爪强，右爪强？
The left or the right claw mm.
左爪或右爪mm。
I can't go to the front.
我不能去前线。
It doesn't let me go that far. Guys.
它不会让我走那么远。 伙计们。
Come I'm.
来我来
Just going to guess.
只是去猜测。
That the left one is stronger and we're going to try to push it,
左边的更强大，我们将尝试推动它，
try to push it in.
试着把它推进去。
Oh, it kind of, kind of works of it.
哦，它有点，有点像它。
It was, it was a little there
是的，有一点
mm just keep doing
嗯，继续这样做，真的。
Just keep nudging it like.
只是继续轻推它。
Yeah, I guess so we just got to.
是的，我想我们只能这样了。
Keep like push pushing off the off the left stick,
像推开左摇杆一样保持，
and then they'll slowly go in right.
然后他们会慢慢地进去。
Are the things I am doing.
是我正在做的事情。
For our furry fucking dog.
为了我们毛茸茸的狗。
OK, ok, ok. OK.
好好好。 好的。
Just like that.
就这样。
Oh, oh, that's.
哦，哦，原来如此。
That was very good.
那非常好。
I think that moved it a little.
我认为这有点动摇了。
Right.
对。
Did it move it a little
有没有移动一点
I don't know.
我不知道。
I think it moved a bit.
我觉得有点动了。
Right.
对。
Just, just a tad bit
只是，只是一点点
it's a nice one.
这是一个不错的选择。
Caufield are oh, this is hard.
考菲尔德是哦，这很难。
God, why did you do this?
上帝，你为什么这样做？
Why did you make it so difficult? God,
你为什么把事情搞得这么难？ 上帝，
I don't think I can do anything from the middle.
我不认为我可以从中间做任何事情。
No, I think in the middle it's not going.
不，我认为中间不会。
I like the furthest I can go is like, right here.
我最喜欢的就是，就在这里。
I'm pretty sure
我很确定
I just got to keep pushing it like that.
我只好继续这样推动它。
Maybe I try the left, the right claw.
也许我试试左爪，右爪。
Let me see if that helps push it. Put
让我看看这是否有助于推动它。 放
it's not even move it
它甚至没有移动它
does that even move it?
这甚至会移动它吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
It moved it a.
它移动了它。
Bit, but then they, like, want backwards, like,
有点，但是他们，就像，想要倒退，像，
oh, no, I didn't move at all.
哦，不，我根本没有动。
It didn't move.
它没有动。
It didn't move. Are
它没有动。 是
look, I'm going to show you guys.
看，我将向你们展示。
It doesn't go that far.
它不会走那么远。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
We'll give us like this see.
我们会给我们这样看。
There's a limit
有一个限制
so doing
所以这样做不会让我到任何地方。
I just had to keep.
我只好坚持。
Pushing its butt down
把它的屁股往下推
oh, I want him.
哦，我想要他。
I really want him, though.
不过，我真的很想要他。
I think. I think I know what I have to do.
我认为。 我想我知道我必须做什么。
I could chi chi.
我可以吃吃喝喝。
Chi Chi chi.
咻咻咻。
I have to go this far.
我必须走这么远。
And then, like. Here
然后，就像。 这里对吗？ 对。
No, why?
没有为什么？
Why is it so hard?
为什么这么难？
Why is it so hard? Oh.
为什么这么难？ 哦。
This is this little guy.
就是这个小家伙。
This little guy. He's not even a little guy.
这个小家伙。 他甚至不是一个小家伙。
He's a big guy. Is just so thick.
他是个大人物。 就是这么厚。
I can't. He's you fat arse.
我不能。 他是你的肥屁股。
Come on, go on.
来吧，继续。
Go into the hole so I can love you.
进入洞里，这样我才能爱你。
Jesus.
耶稣。
What if I'm a woman?
如果我是女人怎么办？
Maybe I tried.
也许我试过了。
The the right claw.
右爪。
Go in.
进去。
No one saw that.
没有人看到这一点。
Nobody saw that.
没有人看到那个。
I hate, hate, hate, hate.
我讨厌，讨厌，讨厌，讨厌。
Hey, Josh, if you're listening,
嘿，乔希，如果你在听，你能喜欢在我们上传
can you like clip that part out from the YouTube video when we upload it?
YouTube 视频时把它剪下来吗？
Thank you. OK, pretend it didn't happen.
谢谢你。 好吧，假装没发生。
I don't know what I don't know what I did there. It was embarrassing.
我不知道我不知道我在那里做了什么。 这很尴尬。
Just just get rid of it, please.
只是摆脱它，拜托。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Oh, oh,
哦，哦，
I feel like my.
我觉得像我的。
Depth perception is an issue here at CNN.
深度感知是 CNN 的一个问题。
I could
我可以
I don't know.
我不知道。
It's someone help.
是有人帮忙。
OK, ok. I'm open. I'm open to.
好的好的。 我是开放的。 我愿意。
Listening to opinions right now.
现在在听意见。
What do we do, guys?
伙计们，我们该怎么办？
What am I supposed to do here?
我应该在这里做什么？
Try and get this one done?
试着完成这个？
Like the round made sense. It was a box.
就像圆是有道理的。 那是一个盒子。
I just, like, shimmy the box around, right?
我只是，喜欢，晃动盒子，对吧？
But this dog is so, like.
但是这只狗就是这样。
Resilience. He doesn't want to go for walkies.
弹力。 他不想去散步。
I'm trying to, like, you know, get on.
我正在努力，就像，你知道的，继续前进。
So go for walkies.
所以去步行吧。
Yes, I want to go
是的，我想去
just push it down the middle.
把它推到中间。
That's all I've been trying to do.
这就是我一直在努力做的。
Oh no.
不好了。
Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。
Chi Chi.
奇奇。
Put the six of all to the left
把所有的六个放在左爪上作为上爪
and trying to.
并试图。
Hit a loop
打一个循环
oh, it doesn't.
哦，它没有。
Work.
工作。
Why doesn't it work, bro?
怎么不行啊老哥
Lift the back.
抬起背部。
I feel like it's too heavy to lift.
我觉得举起来太重了。
He's too.
他也是。
He's too big
他太大了，因为他太大了。 我不。
I can't like, you know, I just.
我不能喜欢，你知道，我只是。
I had to push him.
我不得不推他。
I got to.
我得。
Push a button. Oh,
按下一个按钮。 哦，
I mean, look,
我的意思是，看，
I could try lifting this, but, no, I don't think that's going to be a good idea
我可以试着举起这个，但是，不，我认为这不是一个好主意，你看，我会把他推到更里面。
Right? For
对？ 为了
maybe I got to go.
也许我得走了。
A little further out.
再远一点。
Study beginning and
学习开始和
here you go.
干得好。
That looks like it works, I think.
我认为这看起来很有效。
And all sides.
和所有方面。
We've made no progress.
我们没有取得任何进展。
We've made zero progress.
我们取得了零进展。
Look at that.
看那个。
It's it's still in the same spot since we started
自从我们开始以来它仍然在同一个地方
it kind of it kind of moved a little.
它有点动了。
Bit to the to the right. Right.
位到右边。 对。
It moved a bit OK.
它移动了一点。
All right.
好的。
I feel like I feel like it moved a bit and moved.
我觉得我觉得它移动了一点，移动了。
A slight bit.
一点点。
OK, just ever so slightly, though.
好吧，不过如此轻微。
Some like keep saying try the middle.
有些人喜欢一直说试试中间。
I don't know if that's a good idea.
我不知道这是否是个好主意。
What if I try pushing the middle down.
如果我试着把中间往下推怎么办。
I could.
我可以。
Oh, that did not work.
哦，那没有用。
His butt.
他的屁股。
His body's too big, man.
他的身体太大了，伙计。
His body's way too big.
他的身体太大了。
I can't see anything on the tail that tells not possible.
我在尾巴上看不到任何表明不可能的东西。
I can't, like, pinch the tail.
我不能，比如，捏尾巴。
It's not how the screen gives that.
这不是屏幕给出的方式。
It doesn't work that way.
它不是那样工作的。
Mm oh, man.
嗯，伙计。
Oh, man.
天啊。
Help help.
帮助帮助。
Somebody. Oh, that's good. There
某人。 哦，那很好。 那里
I the only thing I can think of, I'll just keep pushing it.
我唯一能想到的，我会继续推动它。
But there's no progress.
但是没有任何进展。
I keep trying to push
我一直在努力 我一直在努力
on that. I go too far up.
在那。 我走得太远了。
It can go too far.
它可能走得太远。
That's that's fine.
那很好。
It's it's still.
它仍然是。
Pushed it a bit.
推了一下。
I'm just
我只是
like,
像，
what? What do I do?
什么？ 我该怎么办？
What do I do?
我该怎么办？
Pull the tail.
拉尾巴。
Someone says bullets l by Kemp.
有人说坎普的子弹 l。
Pinch it
捏它
guys.
伙计们。
Like I said before, we can't lift the head.
就像我之前说的，我们不能抬起头来。
It doesn't go that far back.
它不会回到那么远。
We can't go for the head.
我们不能去找人头。
Yeah that's a keep trying the bite and I don't know what to do of the bite.
是的，这是一个不断尝试的咬，我不知道该怎么做。
The legs go for the legs
腿为腿而去
my cats.
我的猫。
Maybe they'll be nice to me again.
也许他们会再次对我好。
Maybe.
也许。
Maybe they'll be kind.
也许他们会很友善。
It's lower it. I
它低于它。 一世
oh yeah.
哦耶。
Can I get can you help.
我能得到你能帮忙吗。
Stuff, stuff, stuff.
东西，东西，东西。
Assist, assist, assistance.
协助，协助，协助。
Oh. And
哦。 和
people keep saying go for the white.
人们一直在说去争取白人。
Bars, but I don't know what to do at the white bars.
吧，但我不知道在白色的酒吧做什么。
Right. What I do at the white bars.
对。 我在白酒吧做什么。
Is there something special?
有什么特别的吗？
What's, what's special about the white bars?
白条有什么特别之处？
I can.
我可以。
Move these.
移动这些。
I don't know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办。
Did I help
我有帮助吗
did I help the help?
我帮忙了吗？
I think I helped.
我想我有帮助。
It moved a bit
它移动了一点
oh, my God, it moved a bit.
哦，我的上帝，它移动了一点。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的。
Dude, I.
伙计，我。
Feel like I'm on mad coaching right now because of you guys.
因为你们，感觉我现在正在疯狂执教。
Like, I feel like it's moving.
就像，我觉得它在移动。
I don't know if it's moving or not. Actually,
我不知道它是否在移动。 实际上，
did it move again?
它又动了吗？
I think it did.
我认为确实如此。
Holy shit.
天啊。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
OK, I'll try.
好吧，我会试试的。
I'll try to keep doing that.
我会努力继续这样做。
Because it seems.
因为看起来。
Like it's going to work if I just, you know, pinch hit from the middle.
如果我只是，你知道，从中间捏击它，它就会起作用。
On. Top.
在。 最佳。
The young girl, young.
少女，年轻。
Copy and copy and copy on.
复制和复制并继续复制。
Four.
四。
One, one.
一一。
Come on, come on.
好啦好啦。
Whoa.
哇。
So do I.
我也是。
Do I do good that I do good there.
我做得好，我在那里做得好。
I think I did good there.
我想我在那里做得很好。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
It feels like it's not moving at all.
感觉它根本不动。
I can't tell
我说不出来
I can't tell anymore.
我不能再说了。
Guys, it feels like we're getting nowhere.
伙计们，感觉就像我们无处可去。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Babe, it hasn't moved, so
宝贝，它没有动，所以也许它动了。
I mean, I just got to keep trying.
我的意思是，我必须继续努力。
It like that. Right?
就是这样。 对？
I could mm.
我可以mm。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
All this for a fucking dog.
这一切都是为了一条该死的狗。
It didn't move.
它没有动。
That one did move.
那个确实动了。
Oh, God, it didn't move.
哦，上帝，它没有动。
There a jim over with
有一个吉姆过来
I don't know.
我不知道。
I'm lost my brains.
我失去了我的大脑。
I'm a mind broke tag.
我是一个心碎的标签。
You guys mind broke? Tagged me this game is mine.
你们脑子坏了吧？ 标记我这个游戏是我的。
Broke, tagged me.
坏了，标记我。
I'm just like where
我就像在哪里
I'm trying so hard.
我很努力。
I'm trying so hard to like, you.
我很努力地喜欢你。
Know, calculate the the angles, the the
知道，计算角度，做量子物理学，积分，你。
Know, the quadratic.
知道，二次元。
Equation, the the right angle, the
方程，直角，
the tangents, the Sokoto.
切线，索科托。
The the
该
the the derivative of of his arse.
他屁股的衍生物。
And it's not making any sense
这没有任何意义
like, where do I go, man?
比如，我该去哪里，伙计？
Oh, man.
天啊。
I guess I'll just keep trying for the middle.
我想我会继续尝试中路。
Part.
部分。
And looks like they really want me to go for that gap area.
看起来他们真的希望我去那个空白区域。
Thing.
事物。
He moved.
他动了。
He moved, he moved. He moved. You can't lie to me there.
他动了，他动了。 他动了。 你不能在那里骗我。
He moved a little bit. He moved a little bit. OK, OK.
他稍微动了动。 他稍微动了动。 好的好的。
He's again, he's getting in there.
他又来了，他正在进入那里。
He's getting in there slowly.
他正在慢慢地进去。
It's it's kind of working.
它是一种工作。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Why is this so.
为什么会这样。
Why are you so fat, bro?
大哥你怎么这么胖？
I used to be so chunky.
我以前那么粗壮。
Oh, oh, oh, no, man.
哦，哦，哦，不，伙计。
Old man.
老人。
Maybe, maybe. That it's all yours.
也许，也许。 这都是你的。
Yeah. Taking on a dog years will help.
是的。 接受狗年会有所帮助。
Oh, they're already on pot.
哦，他们已经上锅了。
All right.
好的。
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
来吧，来吧，来吧，来吧。
You know you want to come. You want to you know you want to come home.
你知道你想来。 你想知道你想回家。
Come home with me.
跟我回家吧。
You want to come home with me?
你想和我一起回家吗？
No. Ow, ow, ow. Oh.
不，噢，噢，噢。 哦。
All right, all right.
好吧，好吧。
So what I'm.
那我是什么。
What I'm getting at is I.
我要说的是我。
Have to, like, lift underneath it.
必须，比如，在它下面抬起。
All right? Now,
好的？ 现在，
just keep lifting underneath this.
只要继续在这下面抬起。
Going under shuffle
洗牌
still play.
还在玩。
Crane game is getting me all worked up.
起重机游戏让我兴奋不已。
That didn't do.
那没有。
Anything.
任何事物。
Ah. Oh.
啊。 哦。
Uh that one's.
那个。
In. Do anything, guys.
在。 做任何事，伙计们。
All this, this. This is rough.
这一切，这一切。 这很粗糙。
The phones are off
电话已关机
please, please advise somebody.
请，请告诉某人。
Somebody give me some advice. Mods. It's smart. Predictions. Who?
有人给我一些建议。 模组。 它很聪明。 预测。 谁？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Like, I'm going to get no prediction going.
就像，我不会得到任何预测。
Everyone that says
每个说这句话的人都在说试试狗头。
I can't do that.
我不能那样做。
I've said it so many times already.
我已经说过很多次了。
It doesn't let me go that far.
它不会让我走那么远。
I don't know what.
我不知道。
I it's we have a vulnerable.
我是我们有一个脆弱的。
Vulnerable.
易受伤害的。
Gulf between the bars but keep.
酒吧之间的海湾，但保持。
Shifting between left and right. Claw.
左右交替。 爪。
I just got to shimmy switch.
我刚要摇摆开关。
Between left and right. Claw.
左右之间。 爪。
Huh? Cat OK,
嗯？ 猫好，
ooh, that's good.
哦，那很好。
That's really good.
那真的很好。
That wasn't. Really good.
那不是。 真的很好。
That was not good at all.
那一点都不好。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
If I maybe I try left side now, I would try left side out.
如果我现在尝试左侧，我会尝试左侧。
OK, left side of side.
好的，左侧。
Put that
把那个
all right.
好的。
Oh, no.
不好了。
No, no, no. Ah.
不不不。 啊。
Somebody, are you done?
有人，你说完了吗？
Me basket.
我篮子。
Help, help, help!
救命救命！
God, if there's a God,
上帝，如果有上帝，如果有上帝，请帮助。
Help me help!
帮帮我！
Me God.
我的天。
I can't see anything.
我什么都看不见。
What the hell I really do. It's a pretty nice cell.
我到底在做什么。 这是一个非常漂亮的细胞。
I want to pull on. The tail so bad.
我想拉上。 尾巴太坏了
So it looks really cute, but I can't do anything with the tail
所以它看起来真的很可爱，但我不能用尾巴做任何事情
stuff. Awesome.
东西。 惊人的。
Come calm, please. Please.
请冷静下来。 请。
I need to save my friend.
我需要拯救我的朋友。
He's. He's stuck in. He's stuck in your crane game.
他是。 他被困住了。他被困在你的起重机游戏中。
He's not supposed to be here.
他不应该在这里。
He's supposed to. He's supposed to be with me.
他应该。 他应该和我在一起。
I don't think this is not is not where he's meant to be.
我不认为这不是他应该去的地方。
I'm trying. Get him out of here.
我在尝试。 让他离开这里。
Help!
帮助！
Help! Him!
帮助！ 他！
Maybe if I
也许如果我只是。
I'm pushing would try pushing it again.
我正在推动会尝试再次推动它。
Let's try pushing him down one more time.
让我们再推倒他一次。
Like in closer to the bar.
喜欢靠近酒吧。
You see, it
你看，它看起来像是在做某事，但实际上它并没有做任何事情。
All I'm doing there.
我在那里所做的一切。
Is just, like,
只是，就像，
all really done.
一切都真的完成了。
There is just, like, you know, poking his fat, and it's not.
只是，就像，你知道的，戳他的脂肪，但事实并非如此。
It's not doing much
它没有做太多
that up with them, but up, up.
与他们一起，但是，向上，向上。
This music is going to make me lose it
这音乐会让我失去它直到OK。
I'm just going to try and lift it up from the middle
我只是要尝试每次从中间抬起它。
I don't know, man.
我不知道，伙计。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I can't even tell anymore.
我也说不出来了。
If it moves, it
如果它移动，它
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I can't.
我不能。
I can't even salvage moves it anymore, guys.
伙计们，我什至不能再挽救它了。
I suppose
我想你想让我检查一下爪子
censor the claw.
审查爪子。
Please catch this dog.
请抓住这只狗。
Don't waste my mana fruits.
不要浪费我的法力果实。
I'm shy. I'm going to try my best.
我很害羞。 我会尽力而为。
It's hard out here.
这里很难。
It's really hard out here.
这里真的很难。
Oh. That's a good spot.
哦。 那是个好地方。
That's a really good spot.
那是一个非常好的地方。
Oh, you say, move it, move it, move it.
哦，你说，移动它，移动它，移动它。
Fucking move.
该死的举动。
I saw a fucking move. You can't lie to me now. That fucker moved.
我看到了一个他妈的动作。 你现在不能骗我。 那个混蛋动了。
He moved. Oh, my God.
他动了。 我的天啊。
I saw you, bitch.
我看见你了，婊子。
We made
我们取得了一些进步。
Oh, oh, no.
哦，哦，不。
We got.
我们有。
Like, a figure out. It's
就像，一个数字。 它是
the whole
整体
way. Just keep moving up from the back,
方式。 继续从后面向上移动，就像靠近酒吧的后部一样。
This is such a scoundrel.
这真是个恶棍。
Why am I doing it?
我为什么要这样做？
I'm flying into their into their into their hands. Man.
我飞入他们的手中，进入他们的手中。 男人。
Yeah.
是的。
Hi. Cat
你好。 猫
VI. Want him so bad
六、 好想他
I want I want him so bad.
我想要我想要他那么糟糕。
I want you so bad.
我要你那么坏。
Why is your butt so fat?
为什么你的屁股这么肥？
Why? Why
为什么？ 为什么
what can I do.
我能做些什么。
For what can I do here?
我在这里能做什么？
It's like so it's to make it easier for myself.
就像这样是为了让自己更容易。
I'm not sure.
我不确定。
We've tried everything.
我们已经尝试了一切。
I i backround.
我是背景。
Ok. Left.
行。 左。
Someone said left middle cut.
有人说左中切。
My right there.
我的权利在那里。
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈。
Well.
好。
It's not.
它不是。
It's hmm.
嗯。
I feel like if I give up now.
我觉得如果我现在放弃。
If I give up now,
如果我现在放弃，那是你不会知道的。 哦。
I got to get a air.
我得喘口气。
Yes, you go get help.
是的，你去寻求帮助。
Please help me.
请帮我。
I know you're there.
我知道你在那里。
I know you're watching me suffer you're probably laughing right now.
我知道你在看着我受苦，你现在可能在笑。
He's probably, like, on the or she.
他可能是，喜欢，在或她。
I don't know someone.
我不认识某人。
He's just, like, grinning and smiling at the fact that I'm fucking a up
他只是，就像，对我他妈的一个事实而咧嘴笑着
is, like, a, like, basking.
是，喜欢，一个，喜欢，晒太阳。
In my failure.
在我的失败中。
I can't hear you laugh, but I'm pretty sure you.
我听不见你笑，但我很确定你。
There. Mm.
那里。 毫米。
OK. Uh.
好的。 呃。
Don't give up. I'm not going to give up now.
不放弃。 我现在不会放弃。
We don't give up.
我们不放弃。
We don't give up here.
我们不会在这里放弃。
Quite like you cheering that noise.
很像你为那种噪音欢呼。
And it makes me think like
它让我觉得
it makes me sad.
这让我很难过。
It's no longer joy.
它不再是快乐。
This is not like ram.
这不像公羊。
The Ram box is pretty easy.
Ram 盒子很简单。
It moved a bit again. It moved a little.
它又动了一点。 它移动了一点。
But how many more times are we going to have to do this?
但是我们还要这样做多少次呢？
Why are you being so difficult, bro?
兄弟，你怎么这么难？
How many? How many tries every have.
多少？ 每次尝试多少次。
You given it, by the way?
顺便说一句，你给的？
How many how many tries has it been?
试了多少次了？
Like 50 hmm.
就像 50 嗯。
I think.
我认为。
Like ten.
十个一样。
What do you mean, ten? It's answered ten.
你是什​​么意思，十？ 答案是十。
Ok. OK.
行。 好的。
Push it.
推它。
Push it some.
推一下。
As someone who has spent a lot of money on train games, I think you need to wait.
作为一个在火车游戏上花了很多钱的人，我认为你需要等待。
People play to move it more so you catch it all you will.
人们玩游戏是为了更多地移动它，因此您可以随心所欲地抓住它。
Spent a lot of money on this.
在这上面花了很多钱。
No, I got to. I got to try.
不，我必须。 我得试试。
I got to try. I just got to keep trying.
我得试试。 我只好继续努力。
I fully believe God will show up, ok?
我完全相信上帝会出现，好吗？
We just got to believe in God. We got this.
我们只需要相信上帝。 我们得到了这个。
We can come up and him to help us.
我们可以上来和他一起帮助我们。
Whoever the staff is. They'll come eventually.
不管工作人员是谁。 他们最终会来的。
We'll come around and be like all they feel.
我们会过来，就像他们的感觉一样。
They'll feel bad, right?
他们会感觉很糟糕，对吧？
And be like, oh, this is this little guy.
就像，哦，这就是这个小家伙。
He's trying his best, but he's not get
他正在尽力而为，但他没有得到
he's not getting here.
他不会到这里来。
And then they'll.
然后他们会的。
All they'll throw me a bone to literally throw me a bone.
他们只会给我一根骨头，实际上是给我一根骨头。
Paul I'm stuck.
保罗我被困住了。
Stuck, bro.
卡住了兄弟
I'm still stuck
我仍然卡住
like this.
像这样。
Like I'm a moulding.
就像我是一个模具。
I think I'm moulding weight I actually.
我想我实际上是在塑造体重。
Think
思考
I think I'm moulding and moulding a moulding
我想我正在模塑和模塑一个模塑或不再模塑。
Which I get the copy amount already.
我已经得到了副本金额。
Maybe I should just get the copier now.
也许我现在应该把复印机拿来。
Hold on, hold on. Give me one second.
等一下，等一下。 给我一秒钟。
Give me, like, 2 seconds. OK,
给我，比如，2秒。 好的，
where's my copy? On
我的副本在哪里？ 在
here it is.
这里是。
I found it.
我找到了。
Hold on, hold on, hold on. Give me give me a second.
坚持，坚持，坚持。 给我一秒钟。
Give me a second.
你稍等一会儿。
I'm just.
我只是。
I'm just preparing myself for a really
我只是在为一个真正的
unfortunate.
不幸的。
Oh, my God. Looks so dumb.
我的天啊。 看起来好傻
This looks so dumb.
这看起来很愚蠢。
It looks so stupid.
它看起来很愚蠢。
And why does it look so stupid, man?
为什么它看起来如此愚蠢，伙计？
Oh, no, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不，不，不。
It kicked me out.
它把我踢了出去。
No, it kicked me out.
不，它把我赶出去了。
No, no. The timer. No,
不，不。 计时器。 不，
oh, no, no.
哦，不，不。
The timer. Shit.
计时器。 拉屎。
Please. Oh, fuck.
请。 哦，操。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, no way.
哦，没办法。
I forgot about the timer. I was so.
我忘记了计时器。 我就是这样。
I was so all
我是如此的
oh, that's so sad.
哦，那太可悲了。
Hold on, hold on.
等一下，等一下。
I'm coming back on. Come back. Give me a second.
我回来了。 回来。 你稍等一会儿。
Give me a second. All right.
你稍等一会儿。 好的。
Oh, you God.
哦，你的上帝。
Maybe they didn't.
也许他们没有。
Maybe they didn't realise that there is no God
也许他们没有意识到没有该死的。 一世
I forgot about the time limit.
我忘记了时间限制。
00 my God.
00 我的天。
I got cocked. I got cocked, man.
我上当了。 我被吓到了，伙计。
I got cock so hard.
我的鸡巴太难了。
Hey, hey.
嘿，嘿。
If you're in line.
如果你在排队。
And you can hear this, can you, can you look you can, you can look.
你能听到这个，你能，你能看，你能，你能看。
Can you like you.
你能喜欢你吗。
Lost my spot.
失去了我的位置。
I lost my spot. I'm so dumb I'm so dumb.
我失去了我的位置。 我太笨了，我太笨了。
I forgot, man.
我忘了，伙计。
Help, help.
帮助，帮助。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。
Lift the box from time to time.
不时提起箱子。
You can do it.
你能行的。
Lift the butt soon.
很快抬起屁股。
I got, I got.
我得到了，我得到了。
I got cock though there is a there's.
我得到了公鸡，虽然有一个。
No he's.
不，他是。
Playing now.
现在玩。
I know all
我无所不知
I know.
我知道。
OK, is really just wait here.
OK，真的就是在这里等着。
Just chill out and we here or
放松一下，我们在这里或
what then.
然后怎样呢。
But then what if one of the staff comes in.
但是，如果其中一名工作人员进来怎么办。
And and then I just you know,
然后我只是你知道，
oh, fuck off.
哦，滚蛋。
Fuck.
他妈的。
I think, I think I got I think.
我想，我想我明白了。
I think it's G-men. I don't know.
我认为是G-men。 我不知道。
I can't saw
我看不见
I can't have I can't
我不能拥有我不能
the dogs gone
狗走了
watch and learn.
观看并学习。
What do you mean, watch and learn?
什么意思，边看边学？
Does this person know what they're doing?
这个人知道他们在做什么吗？
Oh, they left.
哦，他们走了。
Oh, they left. Wait, they left. OK, ok, ok.
哦，他们走了。 等等，他们走了。 好好好。
Maybe there's there's a chance. There's a chance.
也许还有机会。 有机会。
I'm like, next in line.
我喜欢，下一个。
I think the other person might be afk
我认为对方可能是 afk
I hope.
我希望。
Oh my god.
我的天啊。
I'm so stupid. I keep.
我太傻了。 我一直。
Why did I just, like, leave my place in lines of fucking love
为什么我只是，喜欢，为了丰富的嗯嗯，把我的位置留在他妈的爱中？
Maybe he gave up.
也许他放弃了。
I think he did give up.
我认为他确实放弃了。
Now there's just one person in front of me.
现在我面前只有一个人。
Come on, come on. Don't, don't, don't.
好啦好啦。 不要，不要，不要。
NCR me. Please don't answer me. Let me have it.
NCR我。 请不要回答我。 让我拥有它。
Let me have it, girl. Go, go. Get out of here.
让我拥有它，女孩。 走，走。 离开这里。
Is he you in there?
他是你在里面吗？
Hello?
你好？
There might be all right.
可能会没事的。
Be gone.
走开。
And C.R..
还有 C.R.
I'm going. I'm going and see Artie.
我要去。 我要去见阿蒂。
Yeah, I just.
是的，我只是。
I just want the dog and and.
我只想要狗和和。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I'm afraid.
恐怕。
Like, stuff is going to pop up here any second now
就像，东西现在随时都会出现在这里，就像，哦，你还在上面。
and, like, oh, you're still on it. But, no, it's not me.
但是，不，不是我。
It's a. Different person. Oh,
它是一个。 不同的人。 哦，
oh, oh, oh, oh.
哦，哦，哦，哦。
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜
Blah, blah. Ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba.
呸呸呸。 巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴。
OK, I'm back, I'm back, baby.
好的，我回来了，我回来了，宝贝。
I'm back, I'm back.
我回来了，我回来了。
I got so scared.
我太害怕了。
I got so scared I was going to lose a dog.
我很害怕我会失去一只狗。
OK, it's not really my god.
好吧，这真的不是我的上帝。
Is this even worth it?
这还值得吗？
Maybe it's a sign. Maybe, guys.
也许这是一个迹象。 也许吧，伙计们。
Maybe it's a. Sign.
也许它是一个。 符号。
That I should just stop
我应该停下来
right?
对？
Because look out.
因为注意。
Look at what happened.
看看发生了什么。
Nothing.
没有。
Nothing happened. It barely moved.
没啥事儿。 它几乎没有动。
It's barely even moved this entire time.
整个过程中它几乎没有移动。
The things I'd seen before
我以前见过的毛绒玩具，因为
just for one.
只为一个。
Big boy
大男孩
every time I do that, it looks like it
每次我这样做时，它看起来都会从前面移动一点，但是。
Don't stop right there.
不要停在那里。
You don't stop.
你不要停下来。
They said don't stop.
他们说不要停下来。
Oh, help, help, help.
哦，救命，救命，救命。
How, how. How.
怎么样，怎么样。 如何。
How how, how
怎么样怎么样怎么样
who do I have to pray to the gotcha?
我必须向谁祈祷？
God's
神
pushing with one arm.
用一只手臂推动。
And that's what I'm trying to do.
这就是我想要做的。
OK, maybe.
好吧，也许吧。
Let me let me try. And.
让我试试。 和。
Push you over here.
把你推到这里。
A bit like right before the bar.
有点像在酒吧之前。
And see if that's like, good enough.
看看这是否足够好。
I kind of did something.
我有点做某事。
It kind of did something, didn't it?
它有点做某事，不是吗？
It looks like it did
看起来确实如此
didn't it?
不是吗？
I can't.
我不能。
Oh, I really don't know.
哦，我真的不知道。
I could.
我可以。
Well,
好，
it looks like it's working.
看起来它正在工作。
It looks like it's working now.
看起来它现在正在工作。
Also a damn. Dog.
也该死。 狗。
Ah ha ha.
啊哈哈哈。
Man, I.
伙计，我。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I feel like I wanna eat. My shoe
我觉得我想吃。 我的鞋子就这个问题。
Yeah, I'm going to eat you. Yummy. No, no.
是的，我要吃掉你。 好吃。 不，不。
I feel like I'm eating my shoe because of this,
因为这个，我觉得我正在吃我的鞋子，
I can't believe it's
我不敢相信要花这么长时间才能得到其中的一只狗。
Just one damn dog. Hmm.
只有一条该死的狗。 唔。
Maybe if.
也许如果。
I move a little bit. More.
我稍微动了动。 更多的。
Over here.
这边。
What that's how that
那是怎么回事
right here.
就在这儿。
Right here, right here.
就在这里，就在这里。
I'm so bad at this.
我在这方面很糟糕。
Oh. I am so bad at.
哦。 我太不擅长了。
This guy's.
这个人的
Like,
像，
I've never had such an issue
我以前从来没有遇到过这样的问题。
He's just so thick
他就是这么厚
this big.
这么大。
This is just so thick.
这太厚了。
I don't.
我不。
I can't even tell that moved him
我什至不能说那感动了他
grab the middle
像以前一样抓住中间，因为实际上是这样工作的。
Didn't work to me.
对我没用。
Grabbing it like that work
像那样抓住它真的是它所做的，
I could did.
我可以做到。
He really did it really work?
他真的做到了吗？
Like right here.
就像这里一样。
So I said keep grabbing like right here and walk slowly.
所以我说像这里一样继续抓着慢慢走。
Oh, my.
天啊。
God. Here. You're working, dude. You're right.
上帝。 这里。 你在工作，伙计。 你说的对。
Oh, my God, you're right.
哦，我的上帝，你是对的。
Holy shit.
天啊。
You're right.
你说的对。
It's kind of there.
有点像。
It's kind of working.
这是一种工作。
This guy.
这家伙。
Oh, my God. I just got it.
我的天啊。 我刚得到它。
OK? Like.
好的？ 像。
Somebody gave me more money.
有人给了我更多的钱。
To gamble
赌一把
feeding my addiction.
喂养我的瘾。
Jesus, man.
耶稣，伙计。
Oh, is it is.
哦，是吗。
Rough out here, boys.
在这里，男孩们。
It's really rough out here.
这里真的很粗糙。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
How much more?
还有多少？
How much more
还有多少
Just give it to me.
就给我吧。
Just give me the dog.
把狗给我吧。
Please, please,
请，请，
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I think you know what?
我想你知道吗？
I think I got to go further.
我想我必须走得更远。
Into the middle
进入中间
I think I need to go further into the yard.
我想我需要深入院子。
To the middle, like in between the bars and the, ah.
到中间，好像在吧台和之间，啊。
The platform kind.
平台类。
OK, let's try that this time.
好，这次我们试试。
Great.
伟大的。
There am.
有。
I work
我工作
kind of, I think.
有点，我想。
I don't know.
我不知道。
He's getting closer
他越来越近了
he's going to walk closer.
他要走得更近了。
Is he?
是他？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Yeah, I don't know.
是的，我不知道。
Is there like a before and after.
有没有前后之类的。
I really want to see the before and.
我真的很想看到之前和。
After from when we started.
从我们开始之后。
It's like to this point, I can't.
到了这个地步，我做不到。
I can't tell
我说不出来
Come on, come on, come on.
来吧，来吧，来吧。
Go, go, go, go. Why,
去去去去。 为什么，
dog, you dog, please.
狗，你的狗，请。
I'm losing faith now.
我现在正在失去信心。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I'm losing faith.
我正在失去信心。
I'm losing so much faith.
我失去了太多的信心。
It's hard.
很难。
It's hard, man.
这很难，伙计。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
All right, all right, all right.
好的，好的，好的。
So what I'm thinking.
所以我在想什么。
About.
关于。
And then I'm going to try.
然后我要试试。
Moving over here a bit and then going for.
稍微移到这里，然后去。
The middle. Maybe that'll help. Like, shimmy over
中间。 也许这会有所帮助。 就像，摇摆不定
oh, god. Why?
天啊。 为什么？
They got to make it so difficult for though.
他们不得不让它变得如此困难。
Oh, mm
哦，嗯
mm mm mm mm.
毫米毫米毫米毫米。
Mm Guys, I can't reach the head.
伙计们，我够不到头。
I don't know how many more times you want me to say I can't reach the head.
我不知道你还要我说多少次我够不到头。
Guys.
伙计们。
I can't go to the head.
我不能去头部。
It cannot go to the head.
它不能到达头部。
You can't, you know, I can't reach that.
你不能，你知道，我达不到那个。
Have you can reach my head.
有没有你能够到我的头。
This fucking dog man.
这该死的狗男
This fucking dog is causing me so much emotional distress.
这只该死的狗给我带来了如此多的情绪困扰。
I need help.
我需要帮助。
Is there, is there help on it.
有吗，有帮助吗。
Can I, can I like ping for help. Hello.
我可以，我可以像 ping 寻求帮助吗？ 你好。
Someone some somebody help.
有人有人帮忙。
Help.
帮助。
So far. 00.
至今。  00.
Mm mm
毫米毫米毫米毫米毫米毫米。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I oh. Ah.
我哦。 啊。
This dog, this god damn dog in this goddamn dog.
这条狗，这条该死的狗中的这条该死的狗。
Please, please, please, please.
请，请，请，请，请。
The please, please just cooperate.
请，请合作。
Just cooperate. With me.
只是合作。 与我一起。
Oh. What am I doing wrong?
哦。 我究竟做错了什么？
I feel like I feel like
我觉得我觉得
it hasn't moved.
它没有移动。
I feel like it hasn't moved in like the past 15 minutes.
我觉得它没有像过去 15 分钟那样移动。
And we're just, like, imagining it
我们只是，就像，想象它
I'm like half of my points
从一开始我们就开始了，现在我的分数已经达到了一半。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, no, no, no. I didn't mean to do that.
哦，不，不，不。 我不是故意的。
Oops.
哎呀。
Oh, did I help?
哦，我有帮助吗？
Did that, like, accidentally help
有没有，比如，不小心帮到了
did that accidentally help it?
这不小心帮到了它吗？
I don't know. That looks like that looks good.
我不知道。 看起来那样看起来不错。
That was kind of good to me.
那对我来说有点好。
No, it didn't.
不，它没有。
It did not.
它没有。
It's it's.
它就是它。
It's fine.
没事。
It's fine. Guys. It's fine.
没事。 伙计们。 没事。
You know, I
你知道，我
because God will God will be here soon.
因为上帝会上帝很快就在这里。
I'm so bad at this.
我在这方面很糟糕。
Oh, my God, I'm so bad.
哦，天哪，我太坏了。
You know, I can hear I can hear my son the back of my head saying
你知道，我能听到我能听到我儿子在我脑后说
sorry God survived
对不起上帝幸存下来
like the entire is just blah.
就像整个只是废话。
Why am I getting so worked up over it?
为什么我对它如此着迷？
Like, just a stupid crane and over him?
就像，只是一个愚蠢的起重机和他？
Jesus
耶稣
Christ.
基督。
Oh, if I go, I don't know where to go for anymore.
哦，如果我去了，我不知道该去哪里了。
Some people say before the bar and some people say after the bar.
有人说在酒吧之前，有人说在酒吧之后。
After they're already after the bar.
之后他们已经在酒吧之后。
Like, right here
就像，就在这里
it's giving me the illusion.
它给了我错觉。
That I'm doing anything at all right now.
我现在正在做任何事情。
Ah, ah, ah.
啊啊啊。
Yeah. Mhm.
是的。 嗯。
Help!
帮助！
Help! Help! Help! Help!
帮助！ 帮助！ 帮助！ 帮助！
Help! Please, please. I've been a good boy.
帮助！ 请，请。 我一直是个好孩子。
I've been.
我已经。
I've been such a good boy.
我一直是一个很好的男孩。
Dude, if I.
伙计，如果我。
If I don't get this.
如果我不明白这一点。
By the end of the stream, I'm going to listen to penis music
在小流结束时，我要听阴茎音乐
like.
像。
Like penis type beats for the rest.
就像阴茎类型的节拍一样。
Of the day.
当天的。
So even like, you know, induce even more of
因此，即使像，你知道的，也会引发更多的精神崩溃。
Oh. Shit man.
哦。 狗屁人。
Get me out.
让我出去。
I give me the dog.
我把狗给我。
Just give it, give it to me, you give it, it needs all.
只要给它，给它给我，你给它，它需要一切。
Got it. Let's all go
知道了。 我们都走吧
what the fuck, man?
什么鬼，伙计？
Remember, if I just.
记住，如果我只是。
Try to it there, I just keep doing what I did before.
在那里尝试，我只是继续做我以前做过的事情。
That seems like.
好像是这样的。
It's. Like your work.
它的。 喜欢你的工作。
Just, like, grab the middle and just keep pulling,
就像，抓住中间，继续拉，
like, right here and there.
就像，在这里和那里。
Like help.
比如帮助。
Like.
像。
That.
那。
It doesn't do anything.
它什么也没做。
It doesn't do anything. Oh.
它什么也没做。 哦。
I thought.
我想。
You know,
你知道，
this is a good time to, ah.
这是个好时机啊。
To show you guys something, though.
不过，给你们看点东西。
I think
我认为
it's the middle of the stream.
它是溪流的中间。
I think I think right now we can take a small moments
我想我想现在我们可以花些时间
to, ah,
到，啊，
so I can show people like a little sneak peek.
所以我可以向人们展示一些偷偷摸摸的东西。
I showed the, um, what's it called
我展示了，嗯，它叫什么
the sobs.
啜泣。
Right.
对。
The Irish showed like the sobs by y'all.
爱尔兰人表现得像你们一样的抽泣。
We're getting new emotes soon, so hold on.
我们很快就会有新的表情，所以请稍等。
Let me see if this
让我看看这是否
the I see this.
我看到了这个。
See, I see.
看，我明白了。
This on the screen
这在屏幕上
drop all the time. Yeah, I know, I know.
一直掉。 是的，我知道，我知道。
But yeah, we're getting new emotes soon.
但是，是的，我们很快就会获得新的表情。
And these are like, this is a sneak peek at a few of them.
这些就像，这是对其中一些的偷窥。
All right.
好的。
Yeah.
是的。
Have you guys enjoy
小伙伴们玩的开心吗
it's so cute, right?
太可爱了，对吧？
It's so fucking adorable. OK, I'll actually hold on.
真是太他妈可爱了。 好吧，我真的会坚持下去。
We're losing time. We're losing time.
我们正在失去时间。 我们正在失去时间。
Put I got to try lifting off from this side again.
让我再次尝试从这边起飞。
You know how
你知道如何
you know
你知道
OK? We didn't get it that time either.
好的？ 那个时候我们也没有得到。
Via look at the emotes.
通过查看表情。
We have a ah.
我们有啊。
A B+ we have a. Big. SOB one.
A B+ 我们有一个。 大的。 呜咽一号。
We have a different kind of head pat and ah Hegel
我们有一种不同的头拍和啊黑格尔
ah he are not taking on a new. Discuss when we got a dog.
啊他不是在接受一个新的。 讨论我们什么时候养狗。
Boy one because you guys one that's all.
男孩一，因为你们就是一。
Boy one and a con for k
男孩一和 k 的骗局
I like not as angry but kind
我喜欢不像敬礼和空气灯那样生气，而是有点生气，这就是你的表情。
She'll be animated.
她会很生气。
Cry. So yeah, I hope you guys are excited for them.
哭。 所以，是的，我希望你们为他们感到兴奋。
I'm excited for them.
我为他们感到兴奋。
We're getting nowhere.
我们无处可去。
You're getting nowhere.
你无处可去。
Oh, I
哦，我
grab from vi.
从 vi 中抓取。
Grab from by.
从旁边抢。
I'll grab his vial.
我会抓住他的小瓶。
All right.
好的。
Yeah, I'm gonna grab his bike
是的，我要抢他的自行车
right here.
就在这儿。
I'll grab it from right there.
我会从那里抓住它。
Why is this so hard
为什么这么难
I've gone so far to lose it all.
我已经走了这么远，失去了这一切。
In the end, it's.
最后，它。
I was in the room all day uh.
我整天都在房间里，呃。
Give it to me, man.
给我，伙计。
Give me the dog.
把狗给我。
Just give me the dog.
把狗给我吧。
There are so many people watching me.
这么多人看着我。
Struggle right now. It's. This is so sad.
马上奋斗。 它的。 这太可悲了。
This is so sad.
这太可悲了。
Help!
帮助！
Help! Help! Help!
帮助！ 帮助！ 帮助！
Help! Advice, advice.
帮助！ 忠告，忠告。
I need advice right now.
我现在需要建议。
What the fuck is out?
什么他妈的出来了？
The fuck do I do about with the Buddha?
我他妈的跟佛陀有什么关系？
With the pa ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba
与啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪啪
I I think I don't know.
我想我不知道。
I think,
我认为，
I don't think that's the thing.
我不认为那是事情。
I don't fucking think her dream the thing.
我他妈的不认为她梦想的事情。
Ah, it's like. Well, this,
啊，好像。 嗯，这个，
this is I press this button.
这是我按下这个按钮。
Well, if I press this button, does it help
好吧，如果我按下这个按钮，有帮助吗
I don't know what this button is supposed to do.
我不知道这个按钮应该做什么。
Does anybody know what this button is supposed to do?
有人知道这个按钮应该做什么吗？
Because, like, it's just sitting here
因为，就像，它只是坐在这里
no. OK, ok, ok. OK.
不。 好好好。 好的。
Chi Chi.
奇奇。
Continue to clamp his arse.
继续夹住他的屁股。
OK, you know what?
好的，你知道吗？
I will continue to clamp his arse.
我会继续夹他的屁股。
Then all that.
那么这一切。
I cannot grab it from the head.
我无法从头上抓住它。
I've said it like 10,000 times now.
我已经说了 10,000 遍了。
It is impossible for me.
这对我来说是不可能的。
The crane doesn't go. Back that far.
起重机不走。 回那么远。
You guys see?
你们看到了吗？
It does not.
它不是。
Go back that far, all right?
回去那么远，好吗？
It doesn't. If you continue to say.
它没有。 如果继续说。
That, I will probably make my mods bonk you so much out.
那，我可能会让我的模组让你非常兴奋。
It just doesn't do it.
它只是不这样做。
I don't know why it's mean.
我不知道为什么它是卑鄙的。
It doesn't let me go back that far. It's sad.
它不让我回去那么远。 这是可悲的。
He really doesn't want me to cry.
他真的不想让我哭。
I just i someone I, I don't know.
我只是我个人，我不知道。
Arse is good. OK, fine. I'll.
屁股不错。 好的。 患病的。
I'll try to keep out the arse
我会尽量不让屁股
I'm getting now.
我现在得到。
I feels like I'm getting.
我觉得我得到了。
Nowhere with the arse though.
虽然没有屁股。
Mm. This is not.
毫米。 这不是。
Working. Is this, is this like.
在职的。 是这样的，是这样的。
How did the how did the other person do it?
对方是怎么做到的？
How the other person gets like
对方是如何走到这一步的。
No way. It's because they got help.
没门。 这是因为他们得到了帮助。
Yeah. Somebody help them.
是的。 有人帮助他们。
Chi chi chi.
咻咻咻。
Chi Chi Chi.
奇奇奇。
I don't have God anymore.
我已经没有上帝了。
God isn't here.
上帝不在这里。
I'm so bad.
我是如此糟糕。
I suck.
我很烂。
I suck at these games.
我很讨厌这些游戏。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不。
This is painful.
这很痛苦。
This is so painful. Guys.
这太痛苦了。 伙计们。
I'm at a loss.
我很茫然。
I'm really lost right now.
我现在真的迷路了。
Like, I feel like we've tried everything and nothing's
就像，我觉得我们已经尝试了一切，但没有任何效果
is because he's such a big boy.
是因为他是个大男孩。
He's such a big boy.
他是个大男孩。
I can't see much about it.
他是个大男孩。 我看不到太多。
I feel like his
我觉得他的前半部分太远了。
I could.
我可以。
I try for, like, around this spot
我试着在这个地方附近，看看我们会看到会发生什么
nothing.
没有。
Happens, nothing.
发生，没有。
Happens.
发生。
And all.
和所有。
Or I.
或者我。
I wonder how is it anybody else?
我想知道别人怎么样？
Is there anybody else that has done this before?
以前有没有其他人这样做过？
And it's like, works for them as far as everybody ever succeeded
就像，只要每个人都成功过，就为他们工作。
Because I.
因为我。
Oh. Oh, wow.
哦。 哦，哇。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Oh, they you oh.
哦，他们你哦。
I'm so. Pleased. Thank you.
我就是这样。 高兴。 谢谢你。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
I'm just I'm crying and crying right now.
我只是我现在正在哭泣和哭泣。
God, thank you, God.
上帝，谢谢你，上帝。
Oh, man. What the fuck do I do now?
天啊。 我他妈现在怎么办？
What is this?
这是什么？
What are what what do I do, guys?
伙计们，我该怎么办？
Oh, hell.
哦地狱。
Oh, oh. What am I supposed to do now?
哦，哦。 我现在该怎么办？
And all had had had just left it lifted from the head
一切都刚刚离开它从头顶抬起
grab it.
抓住它。
Off of the head of the head of the head. OK.
脱了脑袋的脑袋。 好的。
OK, ok, ok. Pug, pug, pug. Paul.
好好好。 哈巴狗，哈巴狗，哈巴狗。 保罗。
Guy could. Go.
盖伊可以。 去。
Oh, thank you.
哦谢谢。
I think he's like, god,
我觉得他就像，上帝，
I'm going to go. Oh,
我要去。 哦，
no, oh,
不，哦，
oh, let's go.
哦，我们走吧。
Y'all.
你们。
We got saved. He came back.
我们得救了。 他回来了。
God came back and helped us.
上帝回来帮助了我们。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
Thor rah da sul rah.
托尔拉达苏拉。
All that Herzog, all that for God's
所有的赫尔佐格，这一切都是为了上帝的小狗。
I want a dog.
我想要一条狗。
Oh, I got. That's our car. We got that. Dog.
哦，我明白了。 那是我们的车。 我们明白了。 狗。
Go for one.
去一个。
How long did that take us?
我们花了多长时间？
Like, an hour.
比如，一个小时。
That really take us an hour.
这真的需要我们一个小时。
Oh, OK, now.
哦，好的，现在。
And I don't know who this is, but somebody else is trying to go for it now, so
而且我不知道这是谁，但现在有人正在努力争取，所以
congratulations. Thank you.
祝贺。 谢谢你。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
OK, now we have two.
好的，现在我们有两个。
Now we have two things we got.
现在我们得到了两件事。
We got a realm wriggle room and we got a dog.
我们有一个领域蠕动室，我们有一条狗。
Now what do I want?
现在我想要什么？
I don't know what I want, man.
我不知道我想要什么，伙计。
Why am I still on this?
为什么我还在这个？
Yes, we got another prise
是的，我们又获得了一个奖品
and another.
和另一个。
Hey. Are over
嘿。 完了
oh, man. Oh.
天啊。 哦。
In a second, I just want to I'm just like, I'm just messaging someone real quick.
在一秒钟内，我只想我就像，我只是在快速向某人发送消息。
Oh, I'm so we have we have a dog now.
哦，我是这样，我们现在有一条狗。
We got the big dog.
我们得到了大狗。
I mean, I have.
我的意思是，我有。
Another dog plushy my own.
我自己的另一只狗毛绒绒。
Now, this one is like, a lot bigger than my other dog plushie.
现在，这个比我的另一只狗毛绒玩具大很多。
So are
也是如此
I moulded or.
我模压或。
Did I suck it?
我吸了吗？
Like, is there?
比如，有吗？
It's just like they come and help you because you suck.
就像他们来帮助你一样，因为你很烂。
So bad or do I to name the dog now?
这么糟糕，还是我现在给这只狗起名字？
I don't know what. To name him.
我不知道。 给他起名。
You guys come up with the name?
你们想好名字了吗？
Yeah, it's our dog now.
是的，它现在是我们的狗。
So if you you want to, like, write some name recommendations in the chat,
所以如果你想，比如，在聊天中写一些名字推荐，
give me some feel free to write it down and I'll, I'll, I'll name him whatever.
给我一些随意写下来，我会，我会，我会命名他。
He's the most popular, I guess
他是最受欢迎的，我猜
yeah.
是的。
Congratulations on finally having it
恭喜你终于拥有了
here. OK.
这里。 好的。
Oh, so instead Chicago
哦，所以芝加哥应该去，应该去，应该去。
Your own name shall go.
你自己的名字会消失。
Shall go.
该走了。
Shall go as she goes.
随她去。
A cute name. And I like it a lot.
一个可爱的名字。 我非常喜欢它。
Yeah.
是的。
Ellen's adorable.
艾伦很可爱。
Oh. Showgirl.
哦。 歌女。
Showgirl.
歌女。
Yeah, I like that.
是的，我喜欢这样。
I mean. I'm very.
我是说。 我很。
Satisfied with what we got so far.
对我们到目前为止所得到的感到满意。
I think if I were to do another one, I think it'd just be one more of.
我想如果我要再做一个，我想它只会再做一个。
I don't know what I would do.
我不知道我会做什么。
There's a big squid. What
有一只大鱿鱼。 什么
wow, that's a big squid.
哇，那是一只大鱿鱼。
And then there's this dude.
然后是这个家伙。
What is he, the son? Real character.
他是什么，儿子？ 真实的性格。
I think
我认为
the penguin.
企鹅。
There's a big elephant seal.
有一只大象海豹。
And there's these weird look in headphones.
耳机中有这些奇怪的外观。
I don't think I want that
我不认为我想要那个
jelly type gift.
果冻型礼物。
What is this?
这是什么？
Hello?
你好？
What is this
这是什么
one? Play
一？ 玩
when I get
当我得到
another blank a lot.
另一个空白很多。
Oh. Oh, OK.
哦。 哦好的。
Ha sure.
哈当然。
I don't this on.
我不这个。
Say, what do I get?
说，我得到什么？
What I get out of that I can't sell.
我不能卖掉的东西。
I said I got. I got like.
我说我得到了。 我喜欢。
Ten free TV and something else.
十个免费电视和其他东西。
OK, cool. Nice.
嗯不错。 好的。
I guess that's.
我猜是这样。
I guess that's fine.
我想那很好。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I think OK.
我觉得可以。
Yeah, some kind of freebie or.
是的，某种免费赠品或。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God. It's a it's a mansaray.
我的天啊。 这是一个曼萨雷。
Or eight.
或八。
It's a.
它是一个。
Stingray.
黄貂鱼。
Yeah, virgin stingray. That's on that ash.
是的，处女黄貂鱼。 那是在那灰烬上。
I got the stingray
我得到了黄貂鱼
no. There's three people playing.
不。 三个人在玩。
Damn, it's.
妈的，就是
I got cocks, man.
我有鸡巴，伙计。
He's a he's.
他是他的。
Adorable, but there's already so many people in line
很可爱，但是排队的人已经很多了
OK, there's that that penguin looks adorable still.
好吧，那只企鹅看起来仍然很可爱。
And what else?
还有什么？
Fantastic. A beast.
极好的。 一个怪兽。
I know who you are.
我知道你是谁。
Kung fu. No, that's jujitsu.
功夫。 不，那是柔术。
Kayson.
凯森。
I was about to say Kung Fu Panda. What
我正要说功夫熊猫。 什么
no, that's not Kung Fu Panda.
不，那不是功夫熊猫。
Ah, mm.
啊，嗯。
There's a hamster.
有一只仓鼠。
An alien. What?
一个外星人。 什么？
There's a fucking zoo. No morphine here.
有一个他妈的动物园。 这里没有吗啡。
Holy shit. I love Xena morphs
天啊。 我喜欢 Xena 变形
mm. What else?
毫米。 还有什么？
I'll see they got here.
我会看到他们来到这里。
Some one look kind of funny.
有些人看起来有点滑稽。
Yeah, a lot of them look kind of funny.
是的，他们中的很多人看起来有点滑稽。
Are a lively sushi backpack, and
是一个活泼的寿司背包，和
that's a joy story.
这是一个欢乐的故事。
You got a friend in me.
你在我里面有一个朋友。
All right.
好的。
Who's this. Guy?
这是谁。 家伙？
Oh, isn't this Inu Maki?
哦，这不是Inu Maki吗？
Oh, I love it.
哦，我喜欢它。
I love you.
我爱你。
The monkey is really cool.
猴子真的很酷。
Uh, what else is there?
呃，还有什么？
I don't know.
我不知道。
All these
这里的这些真的很吸引我啊，我的兴趣
I go back up to the top.
我回到顶部。
Yeah.
是的。
The only thing I saw that kind of
我唯一看到的就是那种
I kind of wanted to go out was that saw the Mansa, another stingray.
我有点想出去是看到曼萨，另一条黄貂鱼。
There's also this big fucking carrot.
还有这个大胡萝卜。
And was this a cushion?
这是一个垫子吗？
An otter?
一只水獭？
Let me take. A look at this one.
让我拿。 看看这个。
What's here?
这是什么？
What the fuck is this? Huh?
这是什么鬼？ 嗯？
Is this one possible um.
这可能吗？
It looks cute.
它看起来很可爱。
Why? I don't know.
为什么？ 我不知道。
All go, like, shove.
都去，就像，推。
My shove my fist. Inside it.
我的拳头。 在里面。
It's a hand warmer.
这是一个暖手器。
Oh, it's a hand warmer. OK,
哦，是暖手宝。 好的，
I know the hole looks kind of saucy.
我知道这个洞看起来有点俏皮。
The hole looks kind of sassy, bro.
这个洞看起来有点时髦，兄弟。
All right,
好的，
I'm gonna I might come back to that one bites.
我要我可能会回到那一口。
What about this who are you?
你是谁呢？
You look really cute.
你看起来真的很可爱。
What kind of a game is this?
这是什么游戏？
A long way.
很长的路。
How is this one work?
这是如何工作的？
Do you guys know how.
你们知道怎么做吗。
What I'm supposed to do here?
我应该在这里做什么？
Am I supposed to knock the the block into the
我应该把街区撞到
into the hole?
进洞？
Yeah.
是的。
She's cute.
她很可爱。
Yeah, she's really cute.
是的，她真的很可爱。
I'm lucky you are, but you look cute.
我很幸运，但你看起来很可爱。
18 centimetres. How big is that?
18 厘米。 那有多大？
That's glued.
那是粘的。
That's a knock.
那是敲门声。
Both of them in or just one of them in
他们都在或只有其中一个在
it is on.
它开着。
Also skim my big.
也略过我的大。
OK, that's not big.
好吧，那不是很大。
OK, load out this one.
好的，加载这个。
There's like two of them.
好像有两个。
Was this one look like huh?
这个是不是很像啊？
What is happening.
怎么了。
Here?
这里？
Oh, what.
啊什么。
We went off and did a cockney
我们走了，做了一个cockney
it says something in Japanese at the top.
它在顶部用日语写了一些东西。
I don't think. All it's because there's always too many people.
我不这样认为。 都是因为人总是太多。
In line. I think
排队。 我认为
there's are a lot of people in line, so I can't get inside.
排队的人很多，我进不去。
I had to push pull the tag off of the hook how.
我不得不把标签从钩子上拉下来。
I seems so difficult
我好像很难
what the heck
有没有搞错
this dude's trying, but it looks so hard.
这家伙正在努力，但看起来很难。
How is that how's that possible?
这怎么可能？
Yeah, this one looks like a scale
是的，这个看起来像秤
I can't.
我不能。
Yeah, I can jump into this one.
是的，我可以跳进这个。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
To knock it off of the platform.
把它从平台上敲下来。
But it was like shaking.
但这就像在颤抖。
All over the place.
到处都是。
Still like that on
还是这样
yeah.
是的。
It's stuck to the platform.
它粘在平台上。
There's no way
不可能
that that looks like it's stuck to the platform.
看起来像是粘在平台上的东西。
Well, you're getting scammed.
好吧，你被骗了。
Sorry. No, not.
对不起。 不，不是。
Not that
不是那个
I want to take a look at Lancer
我想看看Lancer，看看它长什么样。 哦。
What's the Lancer figurine look like?
蓝瑟雕像是什么样子的？
Uh hmm.
嗯嗯。
I like Lancer, but
我喜欢Lancer，但是
I'm not sure
我不确定
I'm really see. Mm.
我真的看到了。 毫米。
Maybe I should just settle for the for the stingray.
也许我应该满足于黄貂鱼。
Right.
对。
Stingray?
黄貂鱼？
Where's a stingray? I'll go back to you.
黄貂鱼在哪里？ 我会回到你身边。
Hey, there you are.
嘿，你来了。
Oh, these are a bunch of people in line for the stingray.
哦，这些是一群为黄貂鱼排队的人。
Why yeah.
为什么是的。
This one doesn't want so bad to get to grab, right
这个不想被抢到，对吧
as I get the dog. I did get the dog.
当我得到狗。 我确实得到了狗。
I got my dog.
我得到了我的狗。
It's going to take an eternity.
这将需要一个永恒。
This one. OK?
这个。 好的？
This guy.
这家伙。
Looks really hard to get.
看起来真的很难买到。
Yeah.
是的。
How are how are you supposed.
你应该怎么样。
To get this one in the whole
为了得到这个整体
we haven't named the dog.
我们还没有给这只狗起名字。
Oh, I think we decide to name him Schlegel.
哦，我想我们决定将他命名为 Schlegel。
Yeah, I think she's gonna be a good name for the dog.
是的，我认为她会成为狗的好名字。
Yeah,
是的，
well, maybe she'll go
好吧，也许她会去
the keys.
按键。
Yeah.
是的。
I don't know about this one, y'all, because there's are people
我不知道这个，你们，因为有人在排队，而且看起来他不会去任何地方
with this
有了这个
he's.
他是。
He can't feel. Anything.
他感觉不到。 任何事物。
I think we just.
我想我们只是。
Since there's are a lot of people waiting, I don't think it's a good idea
由于有很多人在等待，我认为这样做不是一个好主意。
Um. Dude, hold on a second.
嗯。 伙计，等一下。
There's so many ones for Lance.
有很多适合兰斯的。
I really want to try for this one.
我真的很想试试这个。
But there's are, like, a few people.
但也有，比如，几个人。
Waiting in line
排队等候
yeah.
是的。
I can't join this.
我不能加入这个。
Nor I want.
我也不想。
I want to get in here, please. Eggplant.
我想进去，拜托。 茄子。
There is an eggplant.
有茄子。
What brah?
什么布拉？
It's taped.
它被录音了。
What do you mean, it's taped?
什么意思，录音了？
Yeah.
是的。
What is this guy doing here? Uh.
这家伙在这里做什么？ 呃。
I don't know if
不知道这个有没有感觉
all he has to do is just.
他所要做的就是公正。
Get inside the hole, right?
进入洞里，对吧？
Does he have to get both of them or.
他必须得到他们两个还是。
Just one of them?
只有其中之一？
It looks like he has only got one of them, right?
看起来他只有一个，对吧？
I mean, it just says one,
我的意思是，它只是说一个，所以我觉得它有点残忍，
so I wanted to try and get both inside the hole.
所以我想试着把两个都放进洞里。
Both of them.
两个都。
Really?
真的吗？
There's no way.
不可能。
It's just it has to be only one.
只是它必须只有一个。
Right?
对？
Woah.
哇。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Did you see that, guys?
你们看到了吗，伙计们？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
He actually picked it out off the of the crane
他实际上是从起重机上捡来的
but it's stuck there now.
但它现在被困在那里。
I don't know. I think.
我不知道。 我认为。
I don't know if he's going to be able to get it.
我不知道他是否能够得到它。
Holy fuck.
他妈的。
That's funny.
这是有趣的。
That's really funny.
这真的很有趣。
Oh, man, I wanted this so bad.
哦，伙计，我太想要这个了。
I really want to try mhm.
我真的很想试试mhm。
What is he going to do here?
他要在这里做什么？
Oh, sorry, buddy.
哦，对不起，伙计。
Maybe, you know, maybe our staff can come in
也许，你知道，也许我们的工作人员可以进来帮助他们填补所有的空缺。
Are you talking about this eggplant right here?
你是在说这个茄子吗？
Yeah, there's an eggplant right there.
是的，那里有一个茄子。
And then what else?
然后还有什么？
There's
有
gotta
得
your bubble boy.
你的泡泡男孩。
I don't. Know.
我不。 知道。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Who's this guy?
他是谁？
Oh, this the do from Tokyo or Avengers.
哦，这是东京或复仇者联盟的做法。
I like that dude
我喜欢那个哥们
glass. It looks like a candle.
玻璃。 它看起来像一支蜡烛。
I mean, looks like a candle.
我的意思是，看起来像蜡烛。
And I just got another dog hole on.
我刚刚又开了一个狗洞。
Let's see what our other current person is doing with this.
让我们看看我们现在的其他人在做什么。
Yeah, yeah. Look at that. Look at. That.
是啊是啊。 看那个。 看着。 那。
Nothing. Absolutely nothing.
没有。 绝对没有。
We were.
我们曾经。
We were gone for like. 20 minutes from that.
我们就这样走了。  20分钟后。
And they didn't do, they didn't make any progress.
他们没有这样做，他们没有取得任何进展。
That one Sox roll
那个 Sox roll 看起来很难拿到
let's get the dog go
让我们把狗带走
Oh, no,
不好了，
I can't join this one. Mm.
我不能加入这个。 毫米。
Maybe we can try this game again.
也许我们可以再试试这个游戏。
Yeah. Scotty,
是的。 斯科蒂，
but no, it's not, it's not a cluster.
但不，它不是，它不是一个集群。
It's not, it's just the Lancer
不是，只是Lancer
Yeah.
是的。
This one looks bigger than the rim, though.
不过，这个看起来比轮辋大。
It looks a lot.
它看起来很多。
Ah, she looks a lot bigger than rim.
啊，她看起来比rim大很多。
The box that is
那个盒子
so might be a little bit more difficult
所以可能有点困难
mm or up here.
毫米或在这里。
No one's doing this one.
没有人在做这个。
Wait, hold on. No one's doing this.
等等，等等。 没有人这样做。
What do I do here? What? What am I supposed to do here?
我在这里做什么？ 什么？ 我应该在这里做什么？
Someone explain. Somebody tell me. Tell me.
有人解释。 有人告诉我。 告诉我。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
I'm in.
我在。
Oh, my God, I'm in.
哦，天哪，我进去了。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
Knock the card off.
把卡打掉。
The blue to get the card out.
蓝色把卡拿出来。
I just have to get the card out.
我只好把卡拿出来。
Really?
真的吗？
Quick
快的
that doesn't look too bad.
看起来还不错。
Was it
是不是
oh, wait, wait.
哦，等等，等等。
Well, hold up, hold on, hold on, hold on. What?
嗯，坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持。 什么？
What was that?
那是什么？
Did you see that?
你看到了吗？
Chi Chi.
奇奇。
Chi Chi alone?
奇奇一个人？
I have an idea.
我有个主意。
I have. I have an idea.
我有。 我有个主意。
Just trust me, ok?
相信我，好吗？
Just trust me.
相信我。
Oh, I'm stupid.
哦，我很愚蠢。
I'm stupid. I'm stupid. I'm stupid. I went too far. I went too far.
我很蠢。 我很蠢。 我很蠢。 我走得太远了。 我走得太远了。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Yeah, I'm trying to.
是的，我正在努力。
Pull the card.
拉卡。
I'm trying to pull the card right now.
我现在正在尝试拉卡。
But it looks so damn
但它看起来很糟糕
I've never seen a crying game.
我从没见过哭泣的游戏。
Like this one. Put
像这个。 放
diverse things on to you.
各种各样的事情给你。
This one really
这个真的
quite low.
很低。
What the hell
我勒个去
how? It's not moving.
如何？ 它不动。
This one's not moving.
这个不动。
Why is it not moving?
为什么它不动？
Hello?
你好？
What is that sign?
那个标志是什么？
Say, this is my translate.
说，这是我的翻译。
Oh, my God,
我的天啊，
brah.
布拉。
Do you think if I keep at it stuff that God will show up again?
你认为如果我坚持下去，上帝会再次出现吗？
I don't know, I yeah.
我不知道，我是的。
I shouldn't push my luck. See my. Should I?
我不应该碰运气。 见我的。 我是不是该？
I I feel like I really shouldn't push my luck
我觉得我真的不应该碰运气
with God.
与上帝同在。
Oh, my.
天啊。
Goodness.
善良。
When is it coming loose?
什么时候松动？
It feels like it's getting looser.
感觉好像越来越松了。
It looks like it's getting looser, doesn't it?
看起来越来越松了，不是吗？
It's shaking a lot.
它摇晃得很厉害。
Is shaking a lot.
摇晃得很厉害。
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我的天啊。 我的天啊。
Maybe, maybe, maybe I only got.
也许，也许，也许我只有得到。
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持。
I feel like it's that's at his victory party.
我觉得那是在他的胜利派对上。
I'd say that.
我想说的是。
OK. Or maybe I'm under.
好的。 或者也许我在下面。
Some mad culpa on the gun.
枪上有一些疯狂的过失。
No, it's not going out.
不，它不会出去。
Y'all.
你们。
I think I just
我想我只是
dropped my check again.
再次放弃了我的支票。
What's my trick?
我的绝招是什么？
I don't have a trick.
我没有诀窍。
All I'll increase.
我都会增加。
I will.
我会。
Using CP while. Playing will increase arm strength.
一边用CP。 玩会增加手臂力量。
What will increase the.
会增加什么。
Screen arm strength?
屏幕臂力？
Is that what it said?
是这么说的吗？
That sounds stupid.
这听起来很愚蠢。
Could it.
可以吗。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
OK, ok. OK.
好的好的。 好的。
Why is it not moving at all?
为什么它根本不动？
Why is it not moving?
为什么它不动？
It's not.
它不是。
It's not going anywhere.
它不会去任何地方。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Try the left side.
试试左边。
Really? Try the left side.
真的吗？ 试试左边。
Sure, I'll try the left side.
当然，我会试试左边。
Right.
对。
This is so sad.
这太可悲了。
Oh, wait.
等一下。
No, no, no, no.
不不不不。
And move it. Move it. Fucking move. You can't lie to me.
并移动它。 移动它。 该死的举动。 你不能骗我。
They're in fucking move there.
你不能骗我。 他们正在那里他妈的。
I saw it with my own eyes. My own.
我亲眼看到了。 我自己的。
I saw that shit.
我看到了那个狗屎。
Dude, dude, I think we can do it. Oh, my God.
伙计，伙计，我想我们可以做到。 我的天啊。
I stumbled upon a gold mine.
我偶然发现了一座金矿。
Yo, it's possible.
哟，有可能。
It is so possible. What?
这是可能的。 什么？
Or maybe that's how they get you.
或者也许这就是他们得到你的方式。
Don't. Sound so crazy.
不。 听起来很疯狂。
I it's getting loose.
我越来越松了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Guys, guys, guys, it's getting loose.
伙计们，伙计们，伙计们，它变得松散了。
Oh, my God. It's getting looser. And looser.
我的天啊。 它越来越松了。 而且更宽松。
Holy shit.
天啊。
We can do it.
我们可以做到这一点。
Oh, my God. This is crazy.
我的天啊。 这太疯狂了。
That's crazy day.
那是疯狂的一天。
Oh, ha ha ha
哦，哈哈哈
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm.
嗯，嗯，嗯，嗯，嗯，嗯。
It's getting so loose right now.
它现在变得如此松散。
Holy shit.
天啊。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
Oh, yeah, baby.
哦耶宝宝。
Oh, yeah, baby. Oh.
哦耶宝宝。 哦。
It's there.
它就在那里。
The box is, like, wiggling back and forth. It's kind of helping out.
盒子就像来回摆动一样。 这是一种帮助。
Get loose still.
还是松一下吧。
I like that. Wow.
我喜欢。 哇。
Let's try the other side now.
现在让我们试试另一边。
Maybe they'll help.
也许他们会有所帮助。
Why am I so excited over this?
为什么我对此如此兴奋？
This is addictive.
这是上瘾的。
Did I just push it further back in?
我只是把它推回去了吗？
I hope not.
我希望不是。
I can't tell what I just did there.
我不知道我刚刚在那里做了什么。
I push it further back in or I get more loose, and I don't know
我把它推得更深，或者我变得更松，我不知道
now it's still coming out.
现在它仍然出来。
Is this still coming out?
这还要出吗？
I'm not sure.
我不确定。
Stay lofts.
住阁楼。
Keep it on the plus side. Oh.
保持在积极的一面。 哦。
Do what do I like?
做我喜欢的事？
Do I use the left hook or do I use the right hook?
我用左钩还是用右钩？
Original plan.
原计划。
OK, I'll kill it. Six Original plan.
好的，我会杀了它。 六原计划。
Yeah. Yeah, I like that.
是的。 是的，我喜欢这样。
I like that.
我喜欢。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
That's perfect.
那是完美的。
That's so good shot. Boy, you're so sexy.
拍的真好 男孩，你太性感了。
Holy fuck.
他妈的。
Are it's.
是吗。
Giving me. It's giving me so much hope.
给我。 它给了我很大的希望。
And for what?
为了什么？
It's much fucking hope.
真是太他妈希望了。
OK, I'll try it.
好的，我会试试的。
I'll try the left.
我会试试左边。
No. Put
不，放
oh, no, I fucked up.
哦，不，我搞砸了。
I didn't go further in and off.
我没有进进出出。
OK, it's fine. It's fine.
好的，没关系。 没事。
I think we can get it.
我想我们可以得到它。
Before we hit 100,000.
在我们达到 100,000 之前。
Keep ok.
保持好。
Well, this is so thrilling.
嗯，这太令人兴奋了。
Why is this so exciting then?
那为什么会如此令人兴奋呢？
God, it should not be this exciting.
天哪，不应该这么激动人心的。
OK, go, go, go, go.
好的，走，走，走，走。
Come on, come on, come on. Go, go, go.
来吧，来吧，来吧。 去！去！去。
Yes. No.
是的。 不。
No, I didn't go further back enough. OK, ok.
不，我没有走得更远。 好的好的。
I got to go a little bit more back a little bit more back.
我得再往回走一点。
Be a little bit more.
多一点。
Generous of the ah, the distance.
大方的啊，距离。
Oh, well.
那好吧。
What am I getting all. Put.
我得到了什么。 放。
It sore after yo servant if you know
如果你知道蒸粗麦粉，你的仆人会很痛。 啊
that's how it's pronounced
这就是它的发音
bark.
吠。
No I don't think that's good. I don't know.
不，我认为这不好。 我不知道。
I pushed it back in
我把它推回去
I don't think that's a good idea.
我不认为这是一个好主意。
I'm just going to stick to my original plan.
我只会坚持我原来的计划。
Otherwise I'm going to. Troll myself.
否则我会去的。 巨魔自己。
Yeah.
是的。
The other side did a lot better.
对方做得好很多。
In my opinion.
在我看来。
Yeah, that got more loose.
是的，这变得更宽松了。
I just got to keep going at it.
我只得继续努力。
I just got to keep going at that side.
我只得继续在那一边。
Right. Are you?
对。 你是？
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
While it's actually not a scam, can you believe it?
虽然它实际上不是骗局，但你能相信吗？
It's actually not a fucking scam.
这实际上不是一个他妈的骗局。
Well, he's enough
嗯，他够了
all that was not enough.
这还不够。
I look stupid, OK? Ah, cut it.
我看起来很傻，好吗？ 啊，切吧。
Cut it out of it.
把它剪掉。
Cut the cap out.
剪掉帽子。
All the either
所有的
don't look at me. Shut
别看着我。 关闭
I don't fucking look at me.
我他妈不看我。
Don't give me what I want is a little embarrassing.
不给我我想要的有点尴尬。
I can't lie.
我不能说谎。
I fuck up again.
我又搞砸了。
No, ah, my CPR.
不，啊，我的心肺复苏术。
Maybe maybe staff will bless me
也许工作人员会祝福我
God will bless me with his with his love and grace again.
上帝会再次用他的爱和恩典来祝福我。
It's getting there.
它正在到达那里。
I can I can tell it's kind of getting there, though.
不过，我可以说它有点像到达那里。
Maybe I should go for the further back a bit.
也许我应该走得更远一点。
It's like slipping out.
这就像溜出去一样。
You see that it's slowly slipping out. God,
您会看到它正在慢慢滑出。 上帝，
oh, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不。
I messed up. I messed up.
我搞砸了。 我搞砸了。
I didn't mean the press that I fucked up
我不是说我搞砸的媒体
I fucked up, I fucked up I fucked up I fucked up.
我搞砸了，我搞砸了，我搞砸了，我搞砸了。
Fucked up
搞砸了
I look stupid I looked.
我看起来很愚蠢。
So stupid
这么笨
I trusted some soon.
我很快就相信了一些。
All right, let's go again.
好吧，我们再来一次。
Go again.
再去一次。
OK, that's a good spot.
好吧，那是个好地方。
That's a good spot.
那是个好地方。
Right there.
在那里。
Right there,
在那里，
right there, right there, right there.
就在那里，就在那里，就在那里。
Oh. Oh, yo, yo.
哦。 哦，哟，哟。
There's on this one.
有这个。
It's looking. It's looking good.
它正在寻找。 它看起来不错。
It's looking really good.
它看起来真的很好。
Maybe this is the one.
也许这是一个。
Maybe this one's the one. Oh, man,
也许就是这个。 天啊，
I think, I think we can.
我想，我想我们可以。
I think we can get it off.
我想我们可以摆脱它。
All your subjects, he's.
你所有的科目，他都是。
Oh, my God, you're such a tease.
哦，我的上帝，你真是个逗比。
OK, maybe. I mean, maybe I can go.
好吧，也许吧。 我的意思是，也许我可以去。
You know, maybe I can go for the left side now.
你知道，也许我现在可以去左边。
I don't know.
我不知道。
What should I do here?
我应该在这里做什么？
Maybe I should pull up the R at the part that's closer to me.
也许我应该在离我更近的部分拉起 R。
I'm not sure, man.
我不确定，伙计。
Mm mm mm mm mm mm.
毫米毫米毫米毫米毫米毫米。
Or oh, no.
或者哦，不。
I think. Go further enough, OK?
我认为。 走得更远，好吗？
It's fine.
没事。
It's fine. Why?
没事。 为什么？
It's OK.
没关系。
It's OK. The fact that we got.
没关系。 我们得到的事实。
Like, so much progress in such a short amazing is incredible, though.
就像，在如此短暂的惊人中取得如此多的进步是令人难以置信的，尽管如此。
You know,
你知道，
I think that works
我认为这行得通
what? Ow!
什么？ 哦！
Ow, ow, ow.
呜呜呜
Did it get stuck on the left?
是不是卡在左边了？
One got stuck on the bar. Damn, it's
一个被困在了酒吧。 妈的，是
it's kind of tilted, though.
不过，它有点倾斜。
The crane is a.
起重机是一个。
Little bit, like, tilted, I think.
有点，像，倾斜，我想。
I could.
我可以。
Fuck.
他妈的。
I don't know what to do here.
我不知道在这里做什么。
Why are you so jammed in there, huh?
你怎么这么堵在里面，嗯？
Why is he so jammed on the inside?
他的内心怎么这么堵？
What are right?
什么是对的？
Where do I go from here or lofts?
我从这里或阁楼去哪里？
I try lofts.
我尝试阁楼。
Or maybe I could try hooking the ah.
或者，也许我可以尝试挂钩啊。
I could try hooking. The yellow part.
我可以试试钩。 黄色部分。
All right.
好的。
Can I
我可以吗
hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Let me take a look at this.
让我看看这个。
No, the yellow part's too far down.
不，黄色部分太低了。
I don't think. I think.
我不这样认为。 我认为。
I don't think we can reach that
我不认为我们能达到那个
I mean, can we.
我的意思是，我们可以吗？
Get the green part.
获取绿色部分。
Maybe you could get the green
也许你可以得到绿色的绿色圆圈。
The left side.
左侧。
Oh, hold on, hold on.
哦，等一下，等一下。
I have an idea. I have an idea.
我有个主意。 我有个主意。
Like, right there.
就像，就在那儿。
And maybe
有可能
that didn't help.
那没有帮助。
I don't think that helped. We got to.
我认为这没有帮助。 我们得了。
We got to go for the weak link.
我们必须去寻找薄弱环节。
OK, I'll just go for the.
好的，我会去的。
Part that's closest to the bar.
最靠近钢筋的部分。
I think if we loosen that up a bit, it'll
我想如果我们放宽一点，它会
it'll work.
它会工作的。
Put. It right here,
放。 就在这里，
and then
进而
I think that'll work.
我认为这会奏效。
I think this works.
我认为这行得通。
No, it doesn't.
不，它没有。
I think inside the, the little hole fuck
我想在里面，小洞他妈的
perspective is hard man.
透视是硬汉。
Oh my God.
我的天啊。
The perspective is so hard
视角太难了
I know.
我知道。
I missed.
我错过了。
Chi Chi.
奇奇。
I had to be so precise with that whole.
我必须对整体如此精确。
I think we got it
我想我们明白了
no, we didn't.
不，我们没有。
Ah, we're close, though.
啊，虽然我们很接近。
We're getting close to that spot.
我们正在接近那个地方。
I think I just got to get there. Mm
我想我必须到达那里。 毫米
hmm. Hmm.
唔。 唔。
My might've.
我的可能。
It's it's OK.
没关系。
We have plenty of zip put.
我们有很多拉链。
It's all right.
没关系，还不错。
OK, I think that's.
好的，我认为是这样。
I think that's good.
我认为这很好。
What what is that?
那是什么？
Oh, I got the bars cooking me
哦，我让酒吧在煮我
all. I got, bro. Raw.
全部。 我明白了，兄弟。 生的。
The bar, the bar.
酒吧，酒吧。
Talk to me.
跟我说话。
Chi Chi
奇奇
OK? I can't go, like, too far.
好的？ 我不能去，就像，太远了。
Oh, ha ha.
哦，哈哈。
It's like it's tilted a little bit.
好像有点倾斜。
Do you see how the bars position, though?
但是，您看到条形图的位置了吗？
So it's like I'm trying to get right here.
所以这就像我正试图到达这里。
But the way.
但是方式。
Yeah, the way the bars are positioned is so scummy.
是的，酒吧的定位方式是如此肮脏。
OK, I can't go for that one. Pop
好吧，我不能去那个。 流行音乐
ow, ow,
呜呜呜
ow, ow, ow.
哦，哦，哦。
Wait. Why
等待。 为什么
Oh, my god. God, is there.
我的天啊。 天，在吗。
Helping me again?
又帮我了？
Guys, they're helping me.
伙计们，他们在帮助我。
Why? Why do they keep helping me?
为什么？ 为什么他们一直在帮助我？
I just. My that that.
我只是。 我的那个。
Will happen, huh?
会发生的吧？
Although I just all
虽然我只是所有
this is the third time.
这是第三次。
That they've helped me, man.
他们帮助了我，伙计。
Chi chi.
奇奇。
I just.
我只是。
I guess I just.
我想我只是。
Lift it from the back now.
现在从后面提起它。
Right
对
what the heck?
有没有搞错？
Oh, God.
天啊。
I still failed.
我还是失败了。
Too far back.
太远了。
Yeah, a little too far back.
是的，有点太远了。
Cry. But it's all right.
哭。 但没关系。
It's all right. We can get it.
没关系，还不错。 我们可以得到它。
We can get it now.
我们现在可以得到它。
Please.
请。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Oh, I got.
哦，我明白了。
Another one.
另一个。
OK, got
好的，知道了
holy shit.
天哪。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Thank you. Thank you so much.
谢谢你。 非常感谢。
Whoever, whoever is helping me this this much throughout the night,
无论是谁，无论是谁整晚都在帮助我，
you're you're a real one.
你是你是一个真正的人。
I love you. I love you.
我爱你。 我爱你。
Now. Oh.
现在。 哦。
Wow. That's crazy.
哇。 这很疯狂。
So crazy.
如此疯狂。
Oh, man, I.
哦，伙计，我。
I feel.
我觉得。
I feel empowered.
我觉得很有力量。
We hope we still. Have enough points.
我们希望我们仍然。 有足够的积分。
I thought I thought we were.
我以为我以为我们是。
Going to use all of it just to get one.
打算用所有的只是为了得到一个。
But now we got three.
但现在我们得到了三个。
Now oh.
现在哦。
Sheesh.
嘘。
Yeah.
是的。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Thank you. God, we love you.
谢谢你。 上帝，我们爱你。
OK, good luck to the next person that's got to do this.
好的，祝下一个必须这样做的人好运。
Goodbye. I'm going to go somewhere else now.
再见。 我现在要去别的地方。
Ah, well, it's three ok.
啊，嗯，这三个还可以。
Now what to try do.
现在尝试做什么。
We can do one more.
我们可以再做一件事。
We can do. Yeah, we got.
我们能做的。 是的，我们得到了。
We got enough.
我们受够了。
Points for, like, one more one more again.
点，就像，再一再。
This thing, right?
这东西，对吧？
Yeah. Let's go check on this thing right again.
是的。 让我们再次检查一下这件事。
It might be it. Might be possible maybe.
可能就是这样。 也许有可能。
Maybe.
也许。
Hello, Stingray.
你好，黄貂鱼。
You still there?
你还在那儿？
I got reason.
我有理由。
Should I
我是不是该
all know?
都知道吗？
Should I.
我是不是该。
Yeah.
是的。
It's so cool.
太酷了。
I'll get him and look at the boy.
我会得到他，看看男孩。
Oh, uh, I.
哦，我。
I do. Of the. Studio.
我愿意。 的。 工作室。
I had to get him in the hole. Right.
我不得不把他弄进洞里。 对。
It looks really hard to get him in the hole. Mm.
让他进洞看起来真的很难。 毫米。
You think you only I should try, but it's cute.
你认为只有你我应该尝试，但它很可爱。
Yeah.
是的。
This thing are super.
这东西太棒了。
It's horrible, man.
这太可怕了，伙计。
It looks hard.
看起来很难。
It does look hard.
看起来确实很难。
I feel like I might get scammed again.
我感觉我可能又要被骗了。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Before I find. This.
在我找到之前。 这。
Before I try stingray.
在我尝试黄貂鱼之前。
I'm going to go back to the.
我要回去了。
Stingray, but I just want to look at the other ones.
黄貂鱼，但我只想看看其他的。
Oversized, plush elephants.
超大，毛绒大象。
I want to see that what's gone off the elephants
我想看看大象身上发生了什么
zoo. I had to push the card.
动物园。 我不得不推卡。
Inside
里面
is our way.
是我们的方式。
What was this one?
这是什么？
I think I had to push the card inside the ah.
我想我只好把卡推到里面了啊。
Into the hole.
入洞。
Is this one hard? It looks pretty hard.
这个难吗？ 看起来相当难。
All right, now.
现在好了。
Now this one looks like you'll take me forever.
现在这个看起来你会带我永远。
Nothing. You
没有。 你
OK, let's try and go back to Stingray.
好的，让我们试着回到 Stingray。
Unless I see something. That I'm going to look at.
除非我看到了什么。 我要去看看。
I want look. At this figurine. Again,
我要看看 在这个雕像上。 再次，看看如何。
How much progress they've made.
他们取得了多大的进步。
They have made no progress.
他们没有取得任何进展。
These guys are stuck here forever.
这些家伙永远被困在这里。
Dude, we have two cute girls
伙计，我们的购物车里现在有两个可爱的女孩。
Yeah, this one is just preoccupied.
是的，这个只是全神贯注。
This guy's still stuck on the.
这家伙还在坚持。
No. Yeah.
不，是的。
Oh, my God. I feel bad for him.
我的天啊。 我为他感到难过。
He's still stuck trying to get the tag off of the of the box
他仍然被困在试图从盒子上取下标签
or trying to knock it off the the platform.
或试图将其从平台上敲下来。
It's glued, buddy.
是粘的，伙计。
That one has to be glittery.
那个必须是闪闪发光的。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I'm not going to touch that.
我不会碰那个。
Yeah. Let's go. Let's go to the stingray.
是的。 我们走吧。 让我们去黄貂鱼。
It's stingray time.
现在是黄貂鱼时间。
OK, all right.
好的没问题。
How are we going to do this?
我们将如何做到这一点？
How are we going to get our fish to come home?
我们怎样才能让我们的鱼回家？
I feel like we got to go for the sides again, right?
我觉得我们必须再次选择双方，对吧？
Come like this much
来这么多
grab the bite.
咬一口。
Try grabbing the little hole.
试着抓住那个小洞。
Oh, what if we, like, get the the crane into the flaps, right?
哦，如果我们，比如，让起重机进入襟翼，对吧？
Can we get it into the flap of the ah, the thingy?
我们能把它弄进啊，东西的襟翼吗？
Like, without work
就像，没有工作
on? Let me take a look at what's online looking at.
在？ 让我看看网上都在看什么。
What is this part right here?
这部分是什么？
Is this is this like part of its tail?
这是它尾巴的一部分吗？
And what is that? Is that like a trick
那是什么？ 是不是像个把戏
is the tail like taped in with it?
尾巴像用胶带粘住了吗？
Seems kind of heavy pick
似乎是一种沉重的选择
I, I don't, I don't know.
我，我不，我不知道。
Do I get the figure?
我明白这个数字了吗？
I did get the figure.
我确实得到了这个数字。
Yeah, I got 31.
是的，我得到了31。
Three. Tonight.
三。 今晚。
Mm. Pushes
毫米。 推动，但多推动一点，但
chi chi.
奇奇。
Chi Chi. OK.
奇奇。 好的。
Back here
回到这里
so that's you.
那就是你。
Anything. Hold on. I don't know to that.
任何事物。 坚持，稍等。 我不知道。
That's the only thing to the to the.
那是唯一的事情。
Yeah.
是的。
The I think I want to try and push his face
我想我想试着推他的脸
like get my, my the thing in between the bars.
就像得到我的，我的东西在酒吧之间。
Maybe on I have an idea.
也许我有一个想法。
Could I have, I have a big brain idea
我可以吗，我有一个大脑袋的主意
like right.
喜欢对。
In that spot.
在那个地方。
That kind of works
那种作品
yeah.
是的。
I got to push it. Around so that it's like it goes sideways and then I think
我必须推动它。 绕来绕去，就像它横着走，然后我想
if I keep doing it like that he'll, he'll gold it, he'll go down right.
如果我继续那样做，他会的，他会成功的，他会成功的。
Cool.
凉爽的。
Yeah.
是的。
I just got to keep at that, that same method.
我只需要坚持下去，同样的方法。
He's he's getting there slowly.
他是他正在慢慢到达那里。
Slowly. He's rotating.
慢慢地。 他在旋转。
OK, nice.
好的，不错。
Maybe a little bit.
也许一点点。
Less like that much
不像那么多
OK, that's good.
好的，那很好。
I think that's really good.
我认为这真的很好。
No, we are all now.
不，我们现在都是。
I fucked up.
我搞砸了。
I fucked up. Are
我搞砸了。 是
I have like a.
我有喜欢的。
Not a lot of points left though.
不过剩下的分数也不多。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I could. Go.
我可以。 去。
OK that's good. That's good.
好的，那很好。 那很好。
That's really good. That's really good.
那真的很好。 那真的很好。
That's really good.
那真的很好。
It didn't move out much though.
不过，它并没有移出太多。
So I mean,
所以我的意思是，
I maybe we should try.
我也许我们应该试试。
Pushing the but
推但
if I go for the bite.
如果我去咬一口。
Yeah, it's goal let's go to the to the bite
是的，这是我们的目标，让我们去咬一口吧
and see if we can move it. Push
看看我们能不能移动它。 推
hey, that kind of works
嘿，那种工作
it rotated.
它旋转了。
Yeah, OK.
是的，好的。
What I do now.
我现在应该做什么。
What the fuck.
什么鬼。
Do I do now?
我现在做吗？
I could.
我可以。
Maybe like that the his face
也许他的脸就是这样
a little before his face.
在他面前一点。
Oh, I didn't do anything.
哦，我什么都没做。
Now. Are OK.
现在。 没问题。
Maybe I have to go a little bit more.
也许我必须多走一点。
Yeah,
是的，
not too far.
不太远。
It like that much without much is good.
没有太多就这样就好了。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
Oh, wow. OK.
哦，哇。 好的。
The job. Really good job.
工作。 真是好工作。
Very good job. Good job.
干得好。 做得好。
Yeah, ok.
是的，好的。
I think
我认为
just moving on the face.
只是在脸上移动。
Hold on, hold on.
等一下，等一下。
I might sound like I might sound crazy.
我可能听起来像我可能听起来很疯狂。
You're like.
你就像。
Cut I do that
切我这样做
galore.
丰富。
Bit more inside.
里面多一点。
That's.
那是。
Good. That is so Padres.
好的。 就是这样的教士。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Bro, my cock is so far right now.
兄弟，我的鸡巴现在这么远。
OK, I think I should go for.
好吧，我想我应该去。
But yeah.
但是，是的。
I might go for the blood again. Let's go for the blood again.
我可能会再去取血。 让我们再次去取血。
Cut too far
剪得太远
hopefully it wasn't too far.
希望它不会太远。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Not that wasn't.
不是那样的。
I wasn't. OK.
我不是。 好的。
Oh, maybe.
哦，也许吧。
Maybe I should.
也许我应该。
I can push it.
我可以推它。
Maybe I can push it now.
也许我现在可以推动它。
Can I push it.
我可以推一下吗。
Hard enough to push. It i feel like if I push, it's going to get jammed inside.
硬到可以推。 我觉得如果我推，它会被卡在里面。
That seems like a bad idea.
这似乎是个坏主意。
If I, if I if I push right now.
如果我，如果我现在推。
Because pushing too early.
因为推得太早了。
I could. Not.
我可以。 不是。
Not the best idea
不是最好的主意
hmm. Hmm.
唔。 唔。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
哦，哦，哦，哦。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
It is so close.
它是如此接近。
Oh, oh, oh, man.
哦，哦，哦，伙计。
This is getting me excited. Is getting me.
这让我很兴奋。 正在得到我。
It's are really excited.
实在是太激动了。
Give me a hand.
帮帮我。
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
来吧，来吧，来吧，来吧，来吧。
We can get it.
我们可以得到它。
We can get it within the amount that we have.
我们可以在我们拥有的数量之内得到它。
I believe
我相信
it's getting there.
它正在到达那里。
It's slow going there.
去那里很慢。
I'm going to go for the again.
我要再来一次。
Yeah.
是的。
One more time.
再一次。
It's time for the. To the bite.
是时候了。 到咬。
To the bite.
到咬。
But what does it look like?
但它看起来像什么？
It's just like a little section back there.
它就像后面的一个小部分。
It still.
它仍然。
Means
方法
could. OK.
可以。 好的。
That didn't really help much, did it?
这并没有太大帮助，不是吗？
Should I just
我应该只是
oh, the just push it a little push down.
哦，只是把它往下推一点。
I just push it down a little bit. OK.
我只是把它往下推一点。 好的。
Grab it from the middle. Hmm.
从中间抓住它。 唔。
Perfect.
完美的。
And let's see what happens if we do grab it from the middle.
让我们看看如果我们从中间抓住它会发生什么。
Nothing.
没有。
Absolutely nothing. OK,
绝对没有。 好的，
oh, I want to push it so bad, but I don't know.
哦，我想把它推得很烂，但我不知道。
That's a wise thing to do right now.
这是现在做的明智之举。
Cut. Hold on.
切。 坚持，稍等。
Let me try it.
让我试试。
Let me try something stupid.
让我尝试一些愚蠢的事情。
Oh, what do I do here?
哦，我在这里做什么？
Guys?
伙计们？
What do I do here? I'm running out. Zip. Oh.
我在这里做什么？ 我快用完了。 压缩。 哦。
I'm going out.
我要出去了。
I'm running off TV.
我正在逃离电视。
I had to push the button.
我不得不按下按钮。
I'm really.
我真的。
OK. All I'll try.
好的。 我会尝试的。
Do not.
不要。
Then put
然后放
I hope this works.
我希望这行得通。
As well till
直到那是在工作。 不，
that did not work at all.
那根本行不通。
And ask for stuff again.
又要东西了。
I think.
我认为。
I think styles been a little too friendly of me today.
我觉得今天的风格对我来说有点太友好了。
They've helped me three times already,
他们已经帮助了我三次，我获得了三个奖，所以我想我必须自己获得一个。
Maybe.
也许。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I. I think I have.
我，我想我有。
I'll have an idea though.
不过我会有一个想法。
I have a, I have an idea.
我有一个，我有一个想法。
No, it didn't work.
不，它没有用。
I'll know what I do.
我会知道我在做什么。
I was stuck
我卡住了
sure.
当然。
I tried to.
我试过了。
Push his face down
压下他的脸
you know, let's push his face
你知道，让我们推他的脸
I hope this is not a bad idea.
我希望这不是一个坏主意。
Oh. No, it's not work.
哦。 不，这是行不通的。
That's not going to work.
那是行不通的。
Oh, man.
天啊。
Oh, man. Oh, boy.
天啊。 好家伙。
All right, you guys
好吧，你们
I really want to try and.
我真的很想尝试和。
See if I could get the hook in the.
看看我能不能把钩子放进去。
Flops.
翻牌。
You think that's.
你认为是这样的。
I'll be possible.
我将有可能。
I go for his wings.
我去找他的翅膀。
Or his fins, whatever you call it.
或者他的鳍，不管你怎么称呼它。
And see if that works.
看看这是否有效。
I don't.
我不。
I don't think.
我不这样认为。
I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
Shit.
拉屎。
It did something
它做了一些事情
off on the gap. Oh.
关闭间隙。 哦。
I'm running out of points.
我的积分快用完了。
Oh. On guys.
哦。 伙计们。
Oh, no,
不好了，
fuck me.
操我。
It's there in the leg part.
它在腿部。
I tried. I mean we are.
我试过。 我的意思是我们是。
We got the face.
我们得到了脸。
They've they've are this on.
他们有他们有这个。
I don't know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办。
I'll do here. This part right here though.
我会在这里做。 这部分就在这里。
It looks like I can move it a bit.
看起来我可以移动它一点。
I could try moving that a bit.
我可以试着移动一下。
It moves.
它移动。
Oh. And move
哦。 并移动
it'll work to me.
它对我有用。
It works a. Bit.
它有效。 少量。
Yeah.
是的。
It's so we just keep doing that.
所以我们只是继续这样做。
Well go inside.
进去就好。
Put fuck fuck fuck.
放他妈的他妈的。
That's good. That's good. That's good, that's good.
那很好。 那很好。 那很好，那很好。
That's not good.
这是不好的。
Shuffle or.
随机播放或。
Oh boy.
好家伙。
I feel so close of light so far it's ill
我觉得离光太近了，它病了
we have like ten tries left.
我们还剩十次尝试。
Not even ten tries.
甚至十次尝试都没有。
We have like nine. Tries left.
我们有九个。 尝试离开。
Maybe God will come and clutch again.
也许上帝会再来抓紧。
Put on.
穿。
Oh no.
不好了。
Oh no. Oh
不好了。 哦
are on the hall are.
都在大厅里。
I'm running out of plays
我没戏了
although I do
虽然我有
what what I do
我做什么
but it went down a bit.
但它下降了一点。
Oh my God I don't have a lot loved.
哦，我的上帝，我没有太多的爱。
Do I know.
我知道吗。
I don't know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办。
I'm scared I'm so scared.
我很害怕，我很害怕。
I don't know how to push I don't want to.
我不知道怎么推我不想。
Pull I don't want to lift up
拉我不想抬起
push the body. Put.
推身体。 放。
Oh, god.
天啊。
Please tell me this works.
请告诉我这行得通。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
No, that didn't work.
不，那没有用。
I think that's a little too.
我也觉得有点。
You are too inward.
你太内向了。
Are you?
你是？
All these crying games, man?
所有这些哭泣的游戏，伙计？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Where do we go?
我们去哪里？
We go
我们去
if I push the face, you know what happens?
如果我推脸，你知道会发生什么吗？
It just like it's not going to do much.
就像它不会做太多事情一样。
Maybe I should go for back here.
也许我应该回到这里。
If I should go for the back.
如果我应该去后面。
I could put.
我可以放。
Go try lift it out from the back again and see what.
去试试再从后面把它拿出来看看是什么。
Happens.
发生。
It doesn't do anything. Oh.
它什么也没做。 哦。
We got six tries left
我们还有六次尝试
oh, no.
不好了。
We got six tries left home.
我们有六次尝试离开家。
Well, if we don't get it, then there's going to be there's going to be a very.
好吧，如果我们没有得到它，那么将会有一个非常。
Happy customer coming up after me to get it
快乐的顾客来找我
maybe I just got to lift the head up
也许我只需要在你们身边抬起头来。
Now. Work are.
现在。 工作是。
Oh. Oh, no way.
哦。 哦，没办法。
Again,
再次，
all those guys
所有那些家伙
helping me
帮我
what do they just keep?
他们只保留什么？
I feel. I feel like.
我觉得。 我觉得像。
This is so stupid.
这太愚蠢了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
I don't know who you are, but.
我不知道你是谁，但是。
Man, I know if found
伙计，我知道是否找到
the knowing as my back.
知道作为我的后盾。
God does.
上帝会。
Four times. Oh,
四次。 哦，
boy. What the fuck is this?
男生。 这是什么鬼？
So I just push it
所以我只是推它
all? Do I just push it?
全部？ 我只是推它吗？
Do I just push the head in
我只是把头推进去吗
ok? OK, ok.
好的？ 好的好的。
I'm so nervous.
我很紧张。
I only have, like, five tries.
我很紧张。 我只有，比如，五次尝试。
What if I fuck up?
如果我搞砸了怎么办？
The only chance they gave me, I.
他们给我的唯一机会，我。
What.
什么。
Possible
可能的
what? What
什么？ 什么
what will happen there? Oh,
那里会发生什么？ 哦，
I only have one more push.
我只有一推。
Another one, another one.
另一个，另一个。
I only have four tries.
我只有四次尝试。
I only have four more left. Oh.
我只剩下四个了。 哦。
Oh, God. Man.
天啊。 男人。
A form where I feel more left
让我感觉更左的形式
where do I push more the head.
我在哪里推更多的头。
So I push the had more.
所以我推了更多。
I think.
我认为。
I push the head more.
我更推头。
Oh let's
哦，让我们去四次
now for prises.
现在的奖品。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
Oh. So raw.
哦。 太生了
That is crazy.
这很疯狂。
I got I got help
我从儿子那里得到了四次帮助。 这。
The same person.
同一个人。
Is that the same person?
那是同一个人吗？
I don't know. Wow.
我不知道。 哇。
Jesus.
耶稣。
That's amazing, man.
这太神奇了，伙计。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Oh, we got
哦，我们得到了
we got to got to we got to see animal we got a dog
我们必须去 我们必须看到动物 我们有一条狗
and got some cute girls
并得到了一些可爱的女孩
and with some.
和一些。
Money, lots of spare
钱多，闲钱
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
哇，哇，哇，哇，哇。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
And now he's back to his regular position OK, goodbye.
现在他回到了他的正常位置，好的，再见。
What I got. I got.
我得到了什么。 我有。
I got stingray
我有黄貂鱼
I go check my cart.
我去检查我的购物车。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
OK, so down we got saw
好的，所以我们看到了
a stingray.
黄貂鱼。
We got a
我们有一个
an official figurine.
一个官方雕像。
We got ram figurine and we got a Siberian husky
我们有公羊雕像，我们有一只西伯利亚雪橇犬
figurine. Wow.
塑像。 哇。
Oh, that's a lot.
哦，很多。
That's a lot of stuff.
那是很多东西。
A husky very.
很哈士奇。
I mean, a husky of a husky.
我的意思是，哈士奇的哈士奇。
Plushy, plushy.
毛绒绒的，毛绒绒的。
I meant yeah. Wow.
我的意思是是的。 哇。
You know, I thought this was going to be harder, but.
你知道，我以为这会更难，但是。
Hey, listen, guys, guys.
嘿，听着，伙计们，伙计们。
We saw what happened the day they came, and
我们看到他们来的那天发生了什么，并且
the person came and helped
这个人来帮忙
all four times.
全部四次。
Is that is that allowed is that allowed?
那是允许的吗？
I don't know, because, like,
我不知道，因为，就像，
it's every single time somebody came by and was like, hey,
每次有人过来，就像，嘿，
I'm going to help you out
我来帮你
that's crazy, man.
这太疯狂了，伙计。
No. Yeah.
不，是的。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
Whoever you are, if you're watching right now,
不管你是谁，如果你现在在看，如果你在这里
or if you're not watching and you just decide to be a nice person for me.
或者如果你不看，你只是决定对我来说是个好人。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
I'm you made me a very happy boy tonight,
我是你让我今晚成为一个非常快乐的男孩，
sir. Aw, man.
先生。 哦，伙计。
Oh, Parkers.
哦，帕克斯。
I really want to try and go for it.
我真的很想尝试一下。
That was it.
就是这样。
The saw the elephants. Bye.
他们看到了大象。 再见。
I think I'll be too big.
我想我会太大。
It's 42 centimetres.
它是 42 厘米。
How big is that? That's like.
那有多大？ 就是这样。
As huge
一样巨大
as really. Big.
真的。 大的。
Like bigger than most plushies. So
比大多数毛绒玩具都大。 所以
oh, all right.
哦那好吧。
I'm very happy.
我很高兴。
That was fun.
那很有趣。
It satisfied my.
它满足了我的。
My crying game. Addiction.
我的哭戏。 瘾。
My gotcha addiction.
我的陷阱。
Though, having to, like, you know.
虽然，不得不，喜欢，你知道的。
That was about a soul.
那是关于一个灵魂的。
I put down.
我放下了。
$300 for you, for this,
300美元给你，为此，
for this site entire stream.
对于这个网站的整个流。
And we got. Four prises, all that.
我们得到了。 四奖，就是这样。
I think that's worth I think that's pretty worth it.
我认为这是值得的，我认为这是非常值得的。
Right?
对？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Is that worth it?
这值得吗？
I'm not sure.
我不确定。
Like I can't sell for four for prises 300.
就像我不能以 300 的价格卖 4 个。
Not it.
不是。
Seems that.
好像是这样。
OK OK well.
好的好的。
We still we still did it.
我们仍然这样做。
We still got a lot of prises and
我们仍然获得了很多奖品
thank you guys for being my Heitman and for also, like, giving me advice.
谢谢你们成为我的海特曼，也谢谢你们给我建议。
He had the most
他拥有最多
it was.
它是。
It was a lot of fun. Yeah.
这很有趣。 是的。
This is my first time playing, I thought ever.
这是我第一次玩，我想。
So I've never experienced, like,
所以我从来没有经历过，比如，
what it's like.
它是什么样的。
There is definitely some input lag of the whole, like,
整体肯定有一些输入滞后，比如，
you know, trying to
你知道，试图
position the crane correctly.
正确定位起重机。
So that was a little annoying.
所以这有点烦人。
To deal with.
来对付。
But same time, like, once you got used to it, it's ok.
但同时，就像，一旦你习惯了，就可以了。
It's pretty OK.
这还不错。
I don't know what other like thing
我不知道还有什么喜欢的东西
I would have tried to go for but I'm pretty happy.
我本来想去的，但我很高兴。
Yeah, I'm pretty happy with everything we got so far.
是的，我对我们目前所获得的一切感到非常满意。
There's a seal. All
有印章。 全部
this on looks really adorable.
这看起来真的很可爱。
What's an adorable plushie?
什么是可爱的毛绒玩具？
Whenever there's like other ones I missed out on
每当有其他我错过的时候，因为喜欢，我正在查看所有顶级选项。
Nana Boom on you.
娜娜轰隆隆你。
To me, I don't know who that is.
对我来说，我不知道那是谁。
Those are.
那些是。
Those are two people from Demon Slayer
那是恶魔杀手的两个人
and curvy is a curvy plushie.
curvy 是曲线优美的毛绒玩具。
I don't think any of these ones are really that hard.
我不认为这些中的任何一个真的那么难。
It's awesome. Magical.
太棒了。 神奇。
Oh, there's another girl figurine.
哦，还有另一个女孩雕像。
And Goggle
和护目镜
and another. Red one.
和另一个。 重做。
What's this.
这是什么。
One? Looks cute.
一？ 看起来很可爱。
I have no idea what this is.
我不知道这是什么。
Yeah, the one looks really cute, so I'm happy off the the other one that we got.
是的，一个看起来很可爱，所以我很高兴我们得到了另一个。
OK. Wow.
好的。 哇。
And he's a stretcher, but not as enough.
他是一个担架，但还不够。
Yeah. No more crying games.
是的。 没有更多的哭泣游戏。
No more no more crying games for today.
今天没有更多的哭泣游戏。
We are.
我们是。
Denzel, I'm going to close out close out of that,
丹泽尔，我将就此结束，
and I'll see you guys in the bedroom little quick.
我很快就会在卧室见到你们。
All right, just give me a give me a second.
好吧，给我一秒钟。
I check
我检查一下好吗？
Right.
对。
I think
我认为
I think we're good now.
我认为我们现在很好。
All right.
好的。
Oh, that's.
哦，那是。
I still can't.
我还是不行。
Believe, like, they came to help us four times
相信，就像，他们四次来帮助我们
because we just sucked at its overhead.
因为我们只是吸收了它的开销。
At least that's how I felt. Like, like, um.
至少我是这么觉得的。 喜欢，喜欢，嗯。
We were, we were.
我们是，我们是。
Eating arse for the majority of it.
大多数人都吃屁股。
So then on, the person came by and was like, hey, let me help you all
就这样，那个人走过来，说，嘿，让我来帮助你们所有人，就像，这件事，或者你想要的似乎没那么糟糕。
And of the the card one where we had to knock off the card in.
还有一张我们不得不敲掉卡片的卡片。
So the into the hole.
于是入坑。
That one didn't seem too bad. Either.
那个看起来还不错。 任何一个。
So I don't know why they came
所以我不知道他们为什么来帮助我们，但是，嘿，我仍然很感激。
I'm happy.
我很开心。
I'm so happy that they helped us out
我很高兴他们帮助了我们
Donny. Nah.
唐尼。 不。
Yeah, I had a lot of fun tonight and I hope you guys enjoyed it.
是的，今晚我玩得很开心，希望你们喜欢。
Still watching my moulding process, but also
还在看我的成型过程，还
just seeing me fucking elated as hell
只是看到我他妈的兴高采烈
when we got the we actually got the prise,
当我们得到奖品时，我们实际上得到了奖品，
so I didn't want to say
所以我不想说明天是我们的卡拉OK直播。
So if you guys are, you know, interested and come by and hearing me sing
所以如果你们，你知道，有兴趣，过来听我唱歌
some awesome songs, I'm going to be having,
一些很棒的歌曲，我将拥有，它们将被存档，因为我认为它很好。
I don't mind it too much on such days.
在这样的日子里，我不太介意。
I don't know about YouTube.
我不知道 YouTube。
You, too, might be having a little bit trouble with archiving the,
您也可能在存档时遇到了一些麻烦，
um, the karaoke stream, but, you know,
嗯，卡拉 OK 直播，但是，你知道，明天晚上 8 点。
or No.
或没有。
8:30 p.m. EDT or they'll be at 9:30 a.m.
晚上 8 点 30 分 美国东部时间，否则他们将在上午 9:30 到达。
GSD. OK,
GSD。 好的，
I'm going to be trying to sing a lot of songs.
我将尝试唱很多歌。
I don't know how long it's going to last, but we're gonna have a fun time because.
我不知道它会持续多久，但我们会玩得很开心，因为。
It's been a while since.
从那以后已经有一段时间了。
We've sang and I feel like
我们已经唱过了，我觉得为这首歌举办一个很好的庆祝活动会很好，
for all the milestones that we reached recently via having a karaoke.
对于我们最近通过卡拉 OK 达到的所有里程碑。
Because, you know, I want to sing, I feel like singing and some
因为，你知道，我想唱歌，我想唱歌和一些
I've wanted to share
我想和你们分享我这几周学到的一堆新歌。 好的，
I'm watching some, some, some of the old songs
我也在看一些，一些，一些我们以前做过的老歌。
But I want to try and, you know, flex some new ones that we haven't tried before
但是我想尝试并且，你知道，弯曲一些我们以前没有尝试过的新的，因为，你知道，为卡拉
because, you know, it's fun to learn new songs for karaoke.
OK 学习新歌很有趣。
And I do the same old ones every single time, right?
而且我每次都做同样的旧的，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
OK, but I'm going to go and look for so-and-so tonight.
好的，但我今晚要去寻找某某。
If you guys want to join the Discord server.
如果你们想加入 Discord 服务器。
It's up K and also for adorable
K起来了，还有可爱的奖品，期待卡拉OK直播。
Thank you for the fun time today.
谢谢你今天的欢乐时光。
Thank you for coming by.
谢谢你的光临。
It was really fun and I'll be sure get some sleep. OK.
这真的很有趣，我一定会好好睡一觉的。 好的。
I'll read through some.
我会通读一些。
Of the donations and the subs that happened throughout the stream.
在整个流中发生的捐赠和潜艇。
Zero.
零。
Thank you for the arts and the honours.
谢谢你的艺术和荣誉。
And are you singing for the bits bug?
你在为比特虫唱歌吗？
Thank you for the gifts of science maybe.
也许感谢您提供科学的礼物。
Thank you for that.
谢谢你。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Finally I can donate love you feel for all.
最后我可以捐出你对所有人的爱。
For people that don't know.
对于不知道的人。
People that don't have people should be able to donate
没有人的人现在应该可以用卡片捐款，因为我很笨，从来没有像过去那样说出来。
What year plus?
加什么年份？
Because I didn't know I could set up for a card donation and stuff like that.
因为我不知道我可以设置卡片捐赠之类的东西。
So yeah.
是的。
I'm so sorry
我很抱歉
I didn't see that before and I hope it wasn't an inconvenience to anybody
我以前没有看到，我希望这不会给任何人带来不便
that was, you know, doing it before.
你知道，那是以前做过的。
Like, you know,
比如，你知道，
I wanted to donate in the past, but you should be able to now, so yeah.
我过去想捐款，但你现在应该可以了，所以是的。
Vivi, thank you for the demo and
Vivi，谢谢你的演示和
I'm happy for that. I'll know as well.
我为此感到高兴。 我也会知道的。
Glad you like Schlegel every time you read it, you're very happy.
很高兴你每次阅读都喜欢施莱格尔，你很高兴。
It's a cute name for the dog. Yeah.
这是狗的可爱名字。 是的。
Also Sassy.
还有萨西。
Thank you for the 5000 gift subs are red shirt.
感谢您的 5000 份礼物，潜艇是红色衬衫。
Thank you for that. Oh, no, I'm up for thank you for the.
谢谢你。 哦，不，我是来感谢你的。
Oh no as all and that's senior.
哦，不，那是高级的。
Thank you for the it's on now.
感谢它现在正在播放。
He told me thank you for all gift subs for all of you
他告诉我，感谢你们所有的礼物潜艇，因为你们给了社区这么多礼物，他们头晕目眩，只是头晕目眩是的。
Thank you for the big donor as well and E-6 thank you for that Danielle
也感谢您的大捐助者，E-6 感谢您的丹妮尔
Ruff thank you for the snow.
拉夫谢谢你的雪。
I hope you're going to be able to get it.
我希望你能得到它。
Zalgo Mama, I did get the dog overall
Zalgo妈妈，我确实得到了狗
very happy.
很高兴。
That was like the main thing I wanted out of everything.
这就像我想要的一切。
And eventually we got it.
最终我们得到了它。
And it's just so hard, bro,
而且太难了，兄弟，
because, like, how was positioned a somogyi.
因为，就像，如何定位一个 somogyi。
Thank you for that sensor on just obsessional ends.
感谢您在强迫性结束时提供的传感器。
Ray Thank you for the.
雷谢谢你。
Hundred teller donation. I didn't notice that.
百柜员捐款。 我没有注意到这一点。
And for the 10,000 videos. Thank you so much, Ray.
对于 10,000 个视频。 非常感谢你，雷。
No, no.
不，不。
And also hypnosis.
还有催眠。
Thank you for the $50 still.
仍然感谢您的 50 美元。
Yes, I heard your advice and
是的，我听到了你的建议，真正发生的事情是最后的助手。
Yeah, they hit me up in South Korea.
是的，他们在韩国打我。
Thank you for the.
谢谢你的。
Oh no.
不好了。
And Alice, thank you for the deal.
爱丽丝，谢谢你的交易。
Now so please catch this dog.
现在请抓住这只狗。
Are you talking about me or are you talking about the one in the, the machine.
你是在谈论我还是在谈论机器中的那个。
And Zeeshan, thank you for that's all.
Zeeshan，谢谢你。
Not so. And Bye-Bye.
不是这样。 和再见。
Thank you for the 1000 bits and the onic. A.
感谢您提供 1000 位和 onic。 一种。
Unique I'll be having a great day thank you for the 50 ones as well.
独特的我将度过美好的一天，也感谢您的 50 个。
And the help you've been enjoying the screaming, bro.
还有你一直在享受尖叫的帮助，兄弟。
OK, I think I caught up
好的，我想我赶上了今天的所有消息和内容。
I'll catch you guys tomorrow for the karaoke.
明天我会接你们去唱卡拉OK。
OK, have a good night's sleep well and take care.
好的，好好睡一觉，保重身体。
I love you.
我爱你。
Again.
再次。
Be sure to join the discord if you haven't already.
如果您还没有加入不和谐，请务必加入。
Is this gorgeous?
这华丽吗？
I shuttle everybody that is in the server will get up to the announcements on
我穿梭于服务器中的每个人都会收到关于我何时上线的公告
you'll get a sneak
如果您订阅了今晚的手表，您将抢先了解即将发布的内容。
Also be sure to subscribe on YouTube and follow me on Twitter as well.
也请务必在 YouTube 上订阅并在 Twitter 上关注我。
OK, it mean a lot
好的，这意味着很多
and like I said yesterday, we're working on merch.
就像我昨天说的，我们正在开发商品。
I got to talk with Far with a friend
我得和朋友谈远
or like somebody I'm talking to is coordinating with me right now.
或者就像我正在与之交谈的某个人现在正在与我协调。
Let's get some shuttle merch out.
让我们拿出一些穿梭商品。
And Zal, we've decided on a lot of cool things, so if you guys are excited for it,
Zal，我们已经决定了很多很酷的东西，所以如果你们对此感到兴奋，我们将有一个捆绑包，就像这样。
I don't want to.
我不想。
Spoil too much about it, but there's definitely going to be like, you know,
剧透太多了，但肯定会有，你知道，
like first come, first serve exclusive stuff I think would be cool.
喜欢先到先得，我认为会很酷的独家商品。
Like I don't know if people would like signed postcards, but
就像我不知道人们是否想要签名明信片，但是
I think I think like doing a hand signed postcard would be a cool idea, right?
我想我觉得做一张亲笔签名的明信片会是一个很酷的主意，对吧？
So that might be something I'll do for like people
所以这可能是我会为喜欢某些商品的人做的事情。 所以。
Yeah, it's coming.
是的，它来了。
It's I'm really excited man.
这是我真的很兴奋的人。
I can't believe it's finally coming.
我不敢相信它终于来了。
OK, baby, I'm going to look for somebody to read,
好的，宝贝，我要找人看书，但与此同时，我会放一个广告，所以。
Yeah, give me a second. All right.
是的，给我一秒钟。 好的。
Officer Omar, thank you for the gift subs, bro.
奥马尔警官，谢谢你的礼物，兄弟。
Hope you enjoy the stream.
希望你喜欢流。
All right, Barbie
好吧，芭比
you know, for the people that can still see or can still see me
你知道，对于那些仍然可以通过广告看到或仍然可以看到我的人，我正在考虑做一件可爱的小
through the ads, I was thinking of doing, like, a cute little t shirt and
T 恤和
a cap.
一顶帽子。
I was thinking about doing some kind of cap, but I'm not sure.
我正在考虑做某种帽子，但我不确定。
Like, a, like, air, a cotton buckle cap with, like, a curved
Like, a, like, air，棉扣帽，带弧形
and something like a logo on the front or like a tube shuffle or.
和前面的标志之类的东西，或者像管洗牌或。
I was also thinking of, like, acrylic stands and maybe some charms.
我也在考虑，比如亚克力支架，也许还有一些魅力。
Mm. Hmm.
毫米。 唔。
Since I think a lot.
因为想了很多。
Of people, like, acrylic stands.
人之类的，亚克力架子。
Right.
对。
Now, charms are a must.
现在，魅力是必须的。
I always, like, wanna make sure I can.
我总是想确保我能做到。
The charms are like my favourite kind of merch to sell.
吊饰就像我最喜欢出售的商品。
I always try to, you know, get some of that whenever I see
你知道，每当我看到可用的图标、缺点或我所有的朋友都在出售魅力时，我总是试图获得一些。
So yeah, hopefully you guys enjoy the terms when they come out, sell
所以，是的，希望你们在他们出来时喜欢这些条款，卖掉
OK, I think we're going to go and raid.
好的，我想我们要去突袭。
Mm. I'm probably.
毫米。 我大概是。
Gonna go and raid puff pop.
要去突袭泡芙流行音乐。
Tonight.
今晚。
You know, it's Glory Buff Pop
你知道，它是 Glory Buff Pop
since they had a recent art debut,
因为他们最近有了艺术首秀，
I think it'd be really nice to go and show them some love.
我认为去向他们展示一些爱真的很好。
It's been a bit since we've created them, so.
自从我们创建它们以来已经有一段时间了，所以。
Yeah, let's go see what they're up to.
是啊，让我们去看看他们在做什么。
Have a good night, guys.
晚安，伙计们。
Take care. All right.
小心。 好的。
I love you. And I'll see you tomorrow for the karaoke.
我爱你。 明天卡拉OK见。
To be sure. Come by. All right. It's going to.
为了确定。 顺道。 好的。 它会的。
Be a big celebration, and I'm going to be.
成为一个盛大的庆祝活动，我将成为。
We're going to have. Drinks, alcohol.
我们将拥有。 饮料，酒精。
And I might buy some wings to celebrate the occasion.
我可能会买一些翅膀来庆祝这个场合。
So just for just for that night.
所以只是为了那个晚上。
Yeah.
是的。
I mean, like,
我的意思是，就像，
it's it's been a bit.
这是有点。
Since I've, like, had a proper celebration.
因为我已经，喜欢，有一个适当的庆祝活动。
Karaoke.
卡拉OK。
I don't think I've.
我不认为我有。
I've ever had a celebration karaoke, have I?
我曾经有过庆祝卡拉OK，是吗？
It's just been regular karaoke session.
这只是常规的卡拉 OK 会议。
So this one will be, like, our first
所以这将是，就像，我们第一个没有真正官方类型的，像，派对类型的交易。
All right,
好的，
all right.
好的。
Have a good one, guys, and I'll see you tomorrow.
祝你好运，伙计们，我明天见。
I love you, and I'll catch you around, OK?
我爱你，我会抓住你的，好吗？
Sleep well.
睡得好。
If it's Night-Time for you and if it's daytime for you,
如果对你来说是夜间，如果对你来说是白天，
have a good rest of your day. All right?
好好休息一天。 好的？
And thank you for the fun time.
感谢您度过愉快的时光。
Our little arcades in with all the Korean games.
我们的小游戏厅与所有韩国游戏融为一体。
All right?
好的？
Yeah. Thanks for helping me.
是的。 谢谢你帮助我。
And thank you to the staff for helping me, too.
也感谢工作人员对我的帮助。
OK, got to go now.
好的，该走了。
Bye bye.
再见。
Easy bug.
容易的错误。